<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hanifah &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/author/hanifah/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 18:53:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Hanifah &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>The Guilt of Back Pain</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/guilt-back-pain/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/guilt-back-pain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hanifah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 16:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Back Pain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3128</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back pain is such a common ailment that a study in 2012 found that Lower Back Pain (LBP) was the most common cause of disability&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/guilt-back-pain/">The Guilt of Back Pain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back pain is such a common ailment that a study in 2012 found that Lower Back Pain (LBP) was the most common cause of disability worldwide. Other studies show that people who suffer from LBP suffer from the following mental conditions as a direct result: depression, catastrophic cognition, fear of moving or activity, and beliefs about healing. When treated for these conditions, LBP improvement is minimal. A new study is researching the effects of diagnostic uncertainty and guilt related to pain, as an alternative to treatment. Scientists believe with targeting these two areas that patients will see a drastic improvement in overall condition.</p>
<p><span id="more-3128"></span></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-5578" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/faced-with-guilt-2126526_960_720-300x200.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="200" srcset="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/faced-with-guilt-2126526_960_720-300x200.jpg 300w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/faced-with-guilt-2126526_960_720-768x511.jpg 768w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/faced-with-guilt-2126526_960_720-360x240.jpg 360w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/faced-with-guilt-2126526_960_720.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><strong>Diagnostic Uncertainty</strong> is the belief that your condition is misdiagnosed based on a number of factors. This can include doctors not being able to find the actual diagnosis related to the condition. As well as severity of the condition not matching the diagnosis, even if patients agree with the condition. One other prevalent concern is patients feeling as though the diagnosis given by their doctor is incorrect but not feeling confident enough to speak up about it &#8211; among other concerns. With so much uncertainty, patients can have a feeling of general uncertainty, anxiety, and guilt about their condition.</p>
<p>Guilt around a patient&#8217;s condition can be chronic and unexplained, especially when undiagnosed or the diagnosis is uncertain. This extends into relationships and work environments. People experiencing LBP will feel that they&#8217;re making up the condition or something they&#8217;re doing is contributing.</p>
<p>This will increase guilt when a decrease in social time with family and friends decreases or work gets difficult as a result. Isolating based on these feelings will only make the situation worse.</p>
<p>As medicine becomes more and more advanced, doctors are noticing the complex conditions that each of us have in life. Looking at the complete person in a diagnosis and condition, including mental and emotional health will allow physical health to improve. Diet, emotional/mental health, interpersonal relationships, and general wellness all play just as important roles in the overall health of a person as chronic illness does. As we explore our health, the most important practice is to support each other &#8211; even if science cannot explain what we&#8217;re feeling.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/guilt-back-pain/">The Guilt of Back Pain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/guilt-back-pain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3128</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hanifah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 10:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Back Pain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2984</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Portability Perhaps the most obvious use of a portable heating pad is the portable aspect. You don&#8217;t have to worry about plugging them into the wall,&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/">Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: left;">Portability</h2>
<p>Perhaps the most obvious use of a <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">portable heating pad</a> is the portable aspect. You don&#8217;t have to worry about plugging them into the wall, standing in weird positions to get it to the right spot in relation to the cord, and no scary electrical fires to worry about. Which means the uses are as infinite as your ability to carry it. Keep them in cars during the winter in case you break down, in first aid-kits, sleep with them (wrap it in something in case you fall asleep on it &#8211; a sock?), the list goes on and on.</p>
<p><span id="more-2984"></span></p>
<h2> Staying warm in the cold seasons</h2>
<p>During the cold seasons your hands miss out on the warmth of your jacket and double layer of socks on your feet. You can combat this by sticking two of our <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">smaller sized hand</a> warmer Hotshotz into your jacket pockets. Keep them in cars in case of emergencies, just remove them out during the warm months to prevent against any accidental bursts.</p>
<h2>Dilating the Blood Vessels</h2>
<p><a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-5621 alignright" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg" alt="" width="427" height="287" srcset="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg 427w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427-300x202.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 427px) 100vw, 427px" /></a>When you&#8217;re injured, blood cells flood your vessels and kind of sit around the area. In order to increase blood-flow you can apply heat to the area. The cells and vessels in the area will start moving faster creating more space and allowing more flow. This brings additional oxygen, nutrients, and materials to the affected area which helps pain, inflammation, healing, and happiness.</p>
<h2> Stimulating Skin Sensation</h2>
<p>When an injury occurs your pain receptors start firing messages to your brain &#8211; essentially screaming about how there&#8217;s something wrong. One way to help decrease this is to apply heat to the affected area, this causes the receptors to calm down by increasing blood flow and sending parallel messages to the brain &#8211; kind of like distracting your noggin. This works great on your back, check out our <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">large heating pad</a> for help.</p>
<h2>Increasing Flexibility</h2>
<p>Focus on the flexibility of the soft tissue around the affected area &#8211; including muscles and connective tissue, this will help with pain. One way to achieve this is to to apply heat to the area, with portable heating pads. Stiffness occurs when blood-flow to  tissue increases, which decreases flexibility and causes pain. By heating up the area you&#8217;re able to promote circulation and move that blood away from the area &#8211; increasing flexibility and reducing pain.</p>
<p>When you&#8217;re done with the pad, don&#8217;t throw it out! Just boil it until it goes clear again and you&#8217;re all set to use it again! Check out our video below about the <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">HotShotz portable heating pads</a>.</p>
<p><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6mrCihv7wY4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Get your <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">Portable Heating Pads</a> while supplies last!</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/">Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2984</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Reasons to Use a Pregnancy Support Belt</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/pregnancy-support-belt/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/pregnancy-support-belt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hanifah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 10:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Back Pain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maternity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2323</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helps lift the weight of pregnancy while on your feet or working Are you a working parent? Perhaps a single parent that needs to keep&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/pregnancy-support-belt/">10 Reasons to Use a Pregnancy Support Belt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><strong>Helps lift the weight of pregnancy while on your feet or working</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Are you a working parent? Perhaps a single parent that needs to keep the money for bills coming in even during pregnancy? Wearing a pregnancy support belt during your pregnancy will help you redistribute and support the weight of your child while being on your feet for many hours.</p>
<p><span id="more-2323"></span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Supports any extra weight gained during pregnancy and reduces strain from polyhydramnios (excess amniotic fluid)</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Pregnancy isn&#8217;t the same for everyone, nor should it be. Some of us gain more weight than usual or hold excess amniotic fluid. This makes pregnancy a little harder, but let a pregnancy belt will help hold the weight and support your stress.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Carrying more than one child</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>The miracle of childbirth is a blessing to us all, when you get more blessings than you bargained for &#8211; any help can go a long way.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Relieves lower back pack</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>When you become pregnant, your whole body shifts its center of gravity &#8211; like..whoa. Imagine what that&#8217;s doing to your back? The extra strain on your bones and muscles should be supported.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Provide relief for the symptoms of Symphysis Pubis Dysfunction (SPD) or Pelvic Girdle Pain (PGP), common issues during pregnancy</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Symphysis Pubis Dysfunction is a condition of the pelvis where the bones become loose early in pregnancy instead of before the typical pregnancy. Pelvic Girdle Pain is a blanket term for any kind of pelvic/pubic pain experienced by people who are pregnant. These conditions can range from mild to severe, but using a pregnancy support belt may be helpful.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Hip and pelvic pain caused by the release of the hormone relaxin which prepares your body for labor</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>You&#8217;re getting ready to enter the final weeks of pregnancy, and bam! Your hips and pelvis feel like something is coming with a vengeance. If relaxin is supposed to help so much, why does it feel like it&#8217;s beating you up? This is a great time to slip on a pregnancy support belt to shift weight away from the areas and aid in the process.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Relief for sciatica – a common nerve pain which can spread down the back or leg</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Pre-existing conditions or conditions arising from pregnancy can make it that much harder to carry on.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Relief for round ligament pain</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Round Ligament Pain is a common type of pain experienced in the lower belly and groin on one side of your stomach or both.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Support for women who suffer from hernias in pregnancy</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Hernias during pregnancy can happen, check out our other article <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">Different Types of Hernias</a> for more information.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>They can be used to help your muscles strengthen and be supported postpartum</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Okay, you have given birth. You now have a screaming child and aches all over, wasn&#8217;t this supposed to be a blessing? Strap on a pregnancy support belt to help your body acclimate to not carrying a child. As for the screaming baby&#8230; it&#8217;s your partner&#8217;s turn.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><strong><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5637" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pregnant-2763934_960_720.jpg" alt="" width="901" height="720" srcset="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pregnant-2763934_960_720.jpg 901w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pregnant-2763934_960_720-300x240.jpg 300w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pregnant-2763934_960_720-768x614.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 901px) 100vw, 901px" /></strong>Check out our selection of pregnancy belts <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?s=maternity+support+belt&amp;post_type=product">here</a>!</h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/pregnancy-support-belt/">10 Reasons to Use a Pregnancy Support Belt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/pregnancy-support-belt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2323</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ballet vs. Football: The Injuries</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/ballet-vs-football-which-injuries-are-more-severe/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/ballet-vs-football-which-injuries-are-more-severe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hanifah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 15:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2127</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prima or playoff, pointe or pads, bun or ball, these two unsuspecting art forms call for immense talent and drive. As it turns out, the&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/ballet-vs-football-which-injuries-are-more-severe/">Ballet vs. Football: The Injuries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">P<span class="s1">rima or playoff, pointe or pads, bun or ball, these two unsuspecting art forms call for immense talent and drive. As it turns out, the injuries are similar for either sport:</span></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>The Injuries</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"> Stress fractures, tendon injuries, sprains and strains &#8211; ballet isn’t easy, and neither is football. The most common injury areas are: </span></p>
<ul>
<li class="p1"><span class="s1">Ankle sprains</span></li>
<li class="p1"><span class="s1">Knee injuries</span></li>
<li class="p1"><span class="s1">Hamstring injuries</span></li>
<li class="p1"><span class="s1">Hip injuries</span></li>
<li class="p1"><span class="s1">Back injuries</span></li>
</ul>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">A lot of these can be solved with some <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/sprained-ankle-support/">RICE</a>: <em><strong>Relaxation, Ice, Compression, &amp; Elevation</strong></em>. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">With our <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wraps,</a> our <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bernie-bag-with-hotcold-pack/">bernie pouch with hot/cold pack</a> and some pillows and your latest</span><span class="s2"> Netflix binge,</span><span class="s1"> you’ll be on your way to a tour de force no one will forget.</span></p>
<p>When it comes to the game, football player Steve McLendon <a href="http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/steve-mclendon-ballet-is-harder-than-anything-else-i-do/">acknowledges</a> ballet is &#8216;harder than anything else I do&#8217;, but at the end of the day, it&#8217;s not about the injuries, it&#8217;s about the athlete and how quickly they can recover. Regardless of your sport, the products at AT Surgical will get you back in the game.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5670" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ballet-vs-football-1.jpg" alt="" width="750" height="442" srcset="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ballet-vs-football-1.jpg 750w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ballet-vs-football-1-600x354.jpg 600w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/ballet-vs-football-1-300x177.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/ballet-vs-football-which-injuries-are-more-severe/">Ballet vs. Football: The Injuries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/ballet-vs-football-which-injuries-are-more-severe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2127</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 153/163 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-27 18:21:55 by W3 Total Cache
-->