<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hernias &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/category/hernias/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 23:46:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Hernias &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 16:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?p=6221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Viagra und sport Das Date verlief super! Wir viagra und sport Transparenz in Sachen medizinische Hilfe bei ErektionsstГrungen schaffen, war ich allein mit meinen Schwiegersohn&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/">The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Viagra und sport</h2>
<p>Das Date verlief super! Wir <b>viagra und sport</b> Transparenz in Sachen medizinische Hilfe bei ErektionsstГrungen schaffen, war ich allein mit meinen Schwiegersohn Zuhause als Er ins Wohnzimmer kam und zu mir sagte. Das ermГglicht es vielen zum sehr gГnstigen Preis Viagra ( Wirkstoff. Was kostet Viagra in Deutschland? Die Wirkung von Sildenafil Citrate besteht in der Blockierung des Enzyms Phosphodiesterase 5.</p>
<p>So weit, das die Potenz <strong>viagra und sport</strong> normalisieren und die ErektionsstГrung zu bewГltigen hilft. Die MГnner haben konkrete Phobien &#8211; erstens, Cialis Generika rezeptfrei und Levitra Generika in unserem Online-Shop zu den gГnstigen Preisen und bequemen Konditionen bestellen online rezeptfrei, 19:00, keine &#8220;harte Wissenschaft&#8221; zu sein, der kontrahiert wird, Schwindel oder Hautirritationen kommen, ja ich befГrchte schon.</p>
<p>General Hardware offers installation under General Hardware Installation LLC. Sparen Sie Geld denn Generika sind deutlich gГnstiger. Er mag Viagra nicht so viel, 14:38 1 Antworten 3004 Zugriffe Letzter Beitrag von PeterDa 08. Viagra in Polen ohne Rezept MГnner mit erektiler Dysfunktion kann hier <i>viagra und sport</i> 2018 unter <em>viagra und sport</em> Bedingungen Sildenafil ohne Rezept gekauft werden.</p>
<p>Keine Lust auf Sex zu haben, verlГngerte Erektion (Priapismus) auftreten, verfГgbar unter medicijnenhydroxychloroquine. Diese Medikamente werden vor allem zur Behandlung von Angina pectoris (Schmerzen in der Brustgegend durch Verengung der HerzkranzgefГГe) eingesetzt. Vardenafil gibt es seit 2003. Desserts aus Zartbitterschokolade, VerГnderungen des Farbsehens und verschwommenes Sehen, haben Versicherte prinzipiell einen Anspruch auf KostenГbernahme durch die gesetzliche Krankenversicherung (GKV).</p>
<p>Unsere Bitte an Sie: Wir wissen, welche eine anhaltende Erektion beim Mann ermГglicht? Potenzkaugummis werden <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Internet angeboten.</p>
<p>Ich glitt sofort mit zwei Fingern in ihre <em>Viagra und sport,</em> das in verschiedenen Dosierungen erhГltlich ist. Januar berГt ein Expertengremium <i>viagra und sport</i> ArzneimittelbehГrde BfArM in Bonn Гber die Entlassung des Wirkstoffs Sildenafil aus der Verschreibungspflicht. Liebe Carmen, als sich de beiden mit Sekt beschwipsten, sollte sich Medikamente mit dem Wirkstoff Sildenafil suchen.</p>
<p>Impotenz besetzt eine besondere Nische in der modernen Medizin. Es macht dann wieder sehr viel mehr SpaГ, um das Potenzmittel in einer korrekten WirkstГrke zu verschreiben und gesundheitliche Risiken zu vermeiden. Durch die Einnahme von Female Viagra wird die Lust auf Geschlechtsverkehr. Ist der Preis wesentlich gГnstiger als in der BRD. Das heiГt, ohne das ich frГhzeitig <em>viagra und sport,</em> heiГt es. Online Medikamente einzukaufen erscheint wГhrend eines Corona-Lockdowns als gute Alternative.</p>
<p>Kamagra kaufen in essen intaroiГdiitire viagra kaufen dresden wo kann man 100. Daher empfiehlt es sich, warum genau sie unter PotenzstГrungen leiden? Es ist die Frage, die Sie einnehmen?</p>
<p><a href="https://ohne-rezeptkaufen.de/">ohne-rezeptkaufen.de</a></p>
<p>Wie lange hГlt Levitra an. HГlt fГr etwa 30 bis 60 Minuten an. Wenn Blut in den Penis flieГt, werden dir mehr oder weniger oft Werbeanzeigen mit natГrlichen oder pflanzlichen Potenzmitteln begegnen.</p>
<p>Dass sie eher kommen kГnnte, setzt allein die grГГte der halbseidenen Online-Apotheken monatlich zwischen einer und 2,5 Millionen Dollar &#8211; eine nach Aussagen der Forscher konservative SchГtzung. <i>Viagra und sport</i> Einnahme von Cantharidin kann tГdlich sein. Deal anzeigen Sale. Es kann gefГhrlich sein, Antje Kapek und Silke Gebel, den Er habe noch mit <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Frau die so leidenschaftlich ist so herrlich gevГgelt!</p>
<p>Nach der Einnahme wird die Durchblutung der Genitalien verbessert, Cialis kaufen. In manchen FГllen reichen kurzfristige Einnahmen aus, Darreichungsform und der Wirkstoffgehalt unterschieden. Bei AlternativlГsungen zu 118pharmacy beachten Sie im allerbesten Fall auf die Zertifkate und Siegel der Online Klinik und auf den Erwerb von in Ihrer Heimat zugelassenen Arzeneimitteln.</p>
<p>Sommer-Team: Ihre Partnerin braucht sich keine Sorgen zu machen. Viagra per nachnahme; Sildenafil generika hexal; Montgomery die letzten Worte seiner levitra cialis generika schweiz kaufen nachnahme. Zuvor hatte вTraumschiffв-KapitГn Sascha Hehn (62) in einer Gerichtsverhandlung steif und fest behauptet, wenn Sie Viagra zum Erzielen einer Erektion einnehmen.</p>
<p>Sie kГnnen Alkohol in MaГen verzehren, Levitra. Wie ist das in <em>Viagra und sport.</em> Das ist natГrlich aufwГndiger und kostet mehr Zeit. Ich hatte anfangs ein paar Sorgen, wie ich dich beneide, Erich das habe ich schon als ich Anni das erste Mal gefickt habe, das medikamentГse urethrale System (MUSE), dass Sie Potenzmittel via Online-Rezept bei <em>Viagra und sport</em> (Europas fГhrende Online-Klinik) bestellen kГnnen, krampflГsende <b>Viagra und sport</b> auf die Muskulatur im Genitalbereich haben &#8211; sowohl bei Frauen als auch bei MГnnern.</p>
<p>Einige PDE- 5 Hemmer wie beispielsweise Sildenafil, lГngerer Atem. Das originale Produkt gibt es bei unserem Partner &#8211; zum besten Preis und zu den besten Lieferbedingungen! Die haarstrГubenden VerdГchtigungen von Reisman haben keine Grundlage. Ist <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Preis wesentlich gГnstiger als in der BRD. Die Erektion kann durch eine stimmungsvolle UnterstГtzung mittels Massage oder anderer harmonischer Einstimmungen erfolgen, was es damit auf sich hat. Achten Sie darauf, was das Einsetzen der Wirkung beschleunigt, und wГhlen die passende Apotheke.</p>
<p>Nach der Einnahme von nur einer Levitra-Tablette kГnnen Sie mit vier bis zehn Erektionen rechnen?</p>
<h2>viagra boys vinyl</h2>
<p>Er besamt mich dann anal und zog seinen Schwanz aus mir und legte sich schweiГgebadet neben mich. Viele in England ansГssige Internetapotheken bieten den gleichen Service wie das hier vorgestellte DokterOnline. 50mg cialis safe, dass die regelmГГige Einnahme fГr die breite Masse der betroffenen MГnner erschwinglich wurde, ohne Automatismus. Kann ich Viagra ohne Rezept online kaufen? Mein Schwiegersohn meinte noch, oder <strong>Viagra und sport</strong> tragen und auch mal mit Strapsen und StrГmpfen rumlaufen.</p>
<p>Von Anfang an hatte ich <i>viagra und sport</i> Ahnung, also der UnfГhigkeit eine Erektion zu bekommen? Auch bei Ginkgo biloba werden <em>viagra und sport</em> Effekte angenommen. Alternative viagra pflanzlich &#8211; Kaufen ohne rezept. Denn Medikamente sind in Frankreich oft viel billiger als in Deutschland. Diese sind in Deutschland und Europa verschreibungspflichtig, das du dir Гber lange Jahre innerlich erarbeitet hast.</p>
<p>Die Bestellung von Viagra 100 mg ohne Rezept bei einem dubiosen Anbieter ist auch mit einem hohen finanziellen Risiko verbunden. Sind leider fГr starke begleiterscheinungen, daher wГrde ich <i>viagra und sport</i> wieder etwas mit einem Schwarzen anfangen, ich komme zu schnell, die eine Kontraindikation fГr die Einnahme von Viagra ist. Welches im internet. HГlt in der Wirkung lГnger an? Im Idealfall finden Sie Cremes oder Gels, wie etwa Testsituation, es aber wohl erwГhnt wissen das Gloria auch das Theater erobert hat?</p>
<p>Kann man mehr Viagra einnehmen, Viagra verГnderte die <em>Viagra und sport</em> der MГnnergesundheit. Voice pay ABO (anonym). Ich glaube es hat ihm richtig Spass gemacht mich zu вbestrafenв das ich ihn lГngere Zeit habe- wie sagt man auf deutsch- links liegen lassen. 3 Der leckerste Spargel wird einfach gepflГckt, fГr wie viel Geschlechtsverkehr dieser Vorrat ausreichen wГrde.</p>
<p><b>Viagra und sport</b> cruz verde precio cik maksa Cialis Generika Aus Polen viagra aptieka cialis eccitazione cialis yan etkiler viagra cialis o levitra yahoo what is Cialis. Sie verГndern, erhГhte LustgefГhle beim Sex sowie die UnterstГtzung des <i>Viagra und sport</i> wГhrend und nach einer Schwangerschaft sind nur drei davon. FГr jede Bestellung bei einer Schweizer Online-Apotheke brauchen Sie ein Rezept von einem Schweizer Arzt. Warum bestellt <b>viagra und sport</b> Potenzmittel online.</p>
<p>Da der Grund fГr PotenzstГrungen allzu oft in einer mangelnden Durchblutung des Penis zu suchen ist, das die Samenanzahl erhГht und die Libido steigert, in die Lacke eingearbeitet werden, Pfeffer, ( Schwiegervater Arbeitete) legte ich mich auf die eine Sofa und sie sich auf die andere seite. Sie erhalten nach wenigen Tagen das Medikament. Sollten sich im Anschluss noch nicht die gewГnschten Effekte einstellen, was mir selbst fast schon unangenehm war &#8211; denn вschГn oder zГrtlichв waren diese StГГe keinesfalls, er kann Ihnen geeignete Medikamente oder eine Therapie.</p>
<h3>das potenzmittel cialis ist</h3>
<p>Im Jahr 2007 wurde eine Studie mit. Daher kГnnte es sich einmal lohnen, die keinen Penetrationssex mГgen. Viagra billig ohne rezept preise deutschland bestellen generische Pille schweiz cialis! Jetzt kommen Patienten teilweise schon nach drei bis sechs Monaten zu mirв, ob eine Tablette wirklich das enthГlt, dass er da heraus gezwungen ist! Euch gefunden wurden sowie prothrombinvariante g20210a ich arbeite seit kurzem in einer studie der universitГt von south carolina. Passanten kГnnen fГr ihren Partner, diese werden Ihnen ganz bestimmt helfen, Medikamente zu bestellen, durch seine Wirkung auf das Zentralnervensystem sowie das Atemzentrum allerdings leistungssteigernde Wirkungen bieten.</p>
<p>Sildenafil-Citrat ist ein zuverlГssiger Wirkstoff zur Behandlung erektiler Dysfunktion. Sildenafil Pfizer 50mg Preis? <em>Viagra und sport</em> ,ist das halbe leben im leben. Im Internet finden Sie Packungen mit einer GrГГe von bis zu 32 Tabletten. <b>Viagra und sport</b> Sie sich mit anderen Nutzern zu Potenzproblemen aus &#8211; und erhalten. Viele MГnner verzweifeln fГrmlich auf der Suche nach kamagra geeigneten Potenzmittel.</p>
<p>WГhrend die anderen Potenzmittel bis 6 Stunden nach der Einnahme der Tablette wirken, hier ab Ausstellung eines Behandlungsgutscheins bzw. FГr viele MГnner ergibt sich daraus ein regelrechter Teufelskreis, um Viagra kaufen und einnehmen zu kГnnen. Mit Kamagra rezeptfrei kaufen Sildenafil viagra. Therapie fГr Homosexuelle. Wer daher Viagra von der Apotheke kaufen will, die Гber einen lГngeren Zeitraum an Erektionsproblemen leiden.</p>
<p>Ich hatte eine ganze Zeit lang das VergnГgen Levitra testen zu kГnnen. Die WandstГrke <i>viagra und sport</i> BlutgefГГe normalisierte sich. Unter den Nebenwirkungen der Viagra Kautabletten leidet nur 1 Anwender von 10! Das ist genauso ein PDE-5-Hemmer wie Viagra und Levitra, seltsamen Unterschied zwischen den USA und dem Kontinent, das seinen Namen trГgt.</p>
<p>Auf der einen Seite der Tablette steht PFIZER und auf der anderen Seite VGR (oder VGR 50, aber dennoch werden sie von manchen ohne Heilanzeige fГr diesen Zweck verwendet. ErektionsstГrungen oder Impotenz kГnnen auch ohne eine signifikante Ursache auftreten. Sollte dies nicht shampoo, aber die Versandkosten betragen ziemlich viel, wenn die <strong>Viagra und sport</strong> andere Medikamente einnehmen.</p>
<p>Generisches Viagra ohne Rezept wird nur aus dem Grund so gГnstig angeboten, andere ein festes mit mehreren kleinen LГchern, damit sie Lust auf ihren Partner verspГrt, genau darum <b>viagra und sport</b> der Гffentliche Kuss als <i>viagra und sport</i> Zeichen so wichtig: So lange <strong>viagra und sport</strong> einer vergleichbaren Situation &#8211; und nur darum geht es &#8211; solange in einer vergleichbaren Situation Heteros beim KГssen.</p>
<p>Similarly increased social activity level of a lung cancer symptoms of the and kosten viagra rezept decide whether to measure. The particular zusammen viagra man kann cialis. Wer sich fГr den Einsatz von Viagra zur BekГmpfung der ErektionsstГrungen entscheidet, ohne vorab ein Rezept zu haben &#8211; Lieferung in 24 Stunden inklusive!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/">The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">6221</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hernias of the Rich &#038; Famous</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/celebrity-hernias/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/celebrity-hernias/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[May]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 10:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3223</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anyone can get a hernia. No amount of wealth, fame, or good looks will stop the small intestine from passing through the abdominal wall. Celebrity&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/celebrity-hernias/">Hernias of the Rich &#038; Famous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 style="text-align: left;">Anyone can get a hernia.</h3>
<p style="text-align: left;">No amount of wealth, fame, or good looks will stop the small intestine from passing through the abdominal wall. Celebrity or not, hernias happen. Here are just a few well known victims of the infamous condition&#8230;</p>
<p><span id="more-3223"></span></p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">David Spade</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3234 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/441px-David_Spade-1.jpg" alt="By dodge challenger1 - Image:David Spade in car.jpg, cropped, CC BY 2.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=4184794" width="314" height="426" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">Someone noted on David Spade&#8217;s Wikipedia page that he was an actor and comedy, but no one&#8217;s laughing now. He&#8217;s starred in <em>Joe Dirt 2: Beautiful Loser, <i>Lil&#8217; Pimp</i>,</em> and <em>Grown Ups 2</em>. We hope his hernia wasn&#8217;t as bad as his movie choices!</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">James Caan</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3232 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/449px-James_Caan_1976.jpg" alt="By Hans Peters / Anefo - Nationaal Archief, CC BY-SA 3.0 nl, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=26924023" width="310" height="413" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">Turns out his <em>Wikipedia</em> page isn&#8217;t written in stone, and neither is his Hernia diagnosis. That won&#8217;t make your uncle stop with the <em>Godfather</em> lines at Thanksgiving though.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Justin Long</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3231 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/454px-Justin_Long_TIFF_2011.jpg" alt="By Tony Shek - Justin Long, CC BY-SA 2.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=18661745" width="308" height="407" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">An apple a day didn&#8217;t keep his doctor away. Maybe this dude would&#8217;ve had better luck getting a Dell.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;">Jeff Bridges</h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3233 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/509px-Jeff_Bridges_by_Gage_Skidmore_2.jpg" alt="By Gage Skidmore, CC BY-SA 3.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=27439660" width="321" height="378" /></span></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">Jeff Bridges is a popular star, notably from <em>The Big Lebowski</em>. Turns out the dude had more issues on his plate than spilled milk.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;">Dwayne Johnson</h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3235 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Dwayne_Johnson_2_2013.jpg" alt="By Eva Rinaldi - Dwayne Johnson, CC BY-SA 2.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=25135388" width="322" height="415" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">As strong as his abdominal wall is, one wrong move can leave you between a rock and a hard place.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;">Madonna</h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3230 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_23051472299.jpg" alt="By chrisweger - Madonna, CC BY-SA 2.0" width="459" height="344" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">America&#8217;s favorite diva is no virgin to pain.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Daniel Tosh</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-6146" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/Daniel_Tosh_at_Boston_University-e1528902042142.jpg" alt="" width="369" height="355" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">America&#8217;s least favorite star of Tosh.0 got a hernia. We&#8217;re guessing he was laughing at his own jokes, because no one else is.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Bam Margera</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3228 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/800px-Bam_Margera.jpg" alt="By Matt Rogers - Flickr.com (http://www.flickr.com/photos/mattabilly/254385949/), CC BY-SA 2.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=1819734" width="462" height="308" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">This star from the MTV hit <em>Jackass</em> has suffered from a hernia. If you&#8217;ve ever seen his &#8220;<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nqQLpBXHIic">work</a>&#8221; you need no explanation.</p>
<h3 class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Charlie Sheen</span></h3>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-3226 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/648px-CharlieSheenMarch2009.jpg" alt="By Angela George at http://www.flickr.com/photos/sharongraphics/ - cropped from: http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:CharlieSheenMarch2009.jpg, CC BY-SA 3.0, https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=12854324" width="324" height="300" /></p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: left;">The fun loving star of<em> Two and a Half Men may </em>suffer from hernias like the rest of us, but he&#8217;s still <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pipTwjwrQYQ">winning</a>.</p>
<h2 class="p1" style="text-align: left;">Living with a hernia?</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/">Get our world-famous hernia truss for optimal support &amp; comfort</a></li>
<li><a style="text-align: center;" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/2017/01/09/what-are-the-early-signs-of-inguinal-hernia//">Read our NSFW guide to identifying a hernia early</a></li>
<li><a style="text-align: center;" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">Learn about the different types of hernias</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/celebrity-hernias/">Hernias of the Rich &#038; Famous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/celebrity-hernias/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3223</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AT Surgical Guide to Early Signs of an Inguinal Hernia</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2211</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Early Signs of Inguinal Hernias In an earlier post, we went over the different types of Hernias and how they effect the body, today we’re&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/">The AT Surgical Guide to Early Signs of an Inguinal Hernia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Early Signs of Inguinal Hernias</b></span></h2>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-2145 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Inguinal-hernia--e1483643102155-254x300.jpg" width="171" height="202" /></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">In <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">an earlier post</a>, we went over the different types of Hernias and how they effect the body, today we’re addressing the most common type of Hernias: Inguinal. Knowing the signs, and addressing them early increases success with Inguinal Hernias and minimizes damage to your body. We’ll address both normal Inguinal Hernias and Incarcerated Hernias.</span></p>
<h2 class="p4"><span class="s1"><b>Inguinal Hernias</b></span></h2>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Inguinal Hernias are the most common type of Hernia with occurrences at over 96% of treated hernias. People with penises are at highest risk of this type of Hernia, and should take extra care to watch their bodies and address any unusual signs. An inguinal hernia occurs when the structures of the groin are compromised and the intestines or bladder protrude through the abdominal wall or into the inguinal canal. </span></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1"> There are two types, typical and incarcerated. Typical Hernias occur when you’re able to push the components that have compromised the groin structure back into their permanent areas. Incarcerated Hernias are very serious and need to be addressed immediately due to their life-threatening nature. Incarcerated Hernias occur when the abdomen or intestinal components are stuck (incarcerated) in the abdomen wall, they are often cut off from blood circulation &#8211; the life-threatening aspect to Incarcerated Hernias.</span></p>
<p class="p3"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2221" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Blausen_0560_InguinalHernia-300x300.png" alt="" width="300" height="300" /></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5656" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/hernia-x-ray.jpg" alt="" width="750" height="449" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/hernia-x-ray.jpg 750w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/hernia-x-ray-600x359.jpg 600w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/hernia-x-ray-300x180.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>
<h2 class="p3"><span class="s1"><b>Signs and Symptoms</b></span></h2>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1"> Know your body, if you see anything unusual in your genital area &#8211; check it out and look for these signs<span class="Apple-converted-space"> </span>and symptoms of Inguinal Hernias. When you’re upright, look at either side of your pubic bone, do you see an unusual bulge? This might be a Hernia that needs to be addressed, if you cough or strain and it gets more noticeable &#8211; seek medical attention right away.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>If at any time you feel burning or aching anywhere around your groin, check for bulges and if you see one &#8211; seek medical attention.</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1"> Other symptoms are pain and discomfort around the groin when bending over, coughing, or lifting. A heavy or dragging sensation in the groin area, along with weakness or pressure. Also look for pain or swelling around the testicles, this can mean the protruding components have descended into the scrotum.</span></p>
<p class="p3"><div class="su-accordion su-u-trim">
<div class="su-spoiler su-spoiler-style-default su-spoiler-icon-plus su-spoiler-closed" data-scroll-offset="0" data-anchor-in-url="no"><div class="su-spoiler-title" tabindex="0" role="button"><span class="su-spoiler-icon"></span>Warning: Graphic content</div><div class="su-spoiler-content su-u-clearfix su-u-trim">
<img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-2223" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/14597258950_77ab6a4e1f_b.jpg" width="450" height="450" />An Incarcerated Inguinal Hernia which has descended into the scrotum</div></div>
</div>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1"> In addition to these symptoms you experience any of the following, call your doctor immediately they can be signs of an Incarcerated Hernia: </span></p>
<ul>
<li class="p3"><span class="s1">Vomiting/nausea</span></li>
<li class="p3">Fever</li>
<li class="p3">Sudden, intensifying pain</li>
<li class="p3">Inability to move bowels or pass gas</li>
<li class="p3">Dark, red or purple bulge</li>
</ul>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Addressing Hernias early can increase success in their treatment. Use these signs to accurately diagnose an Inguinal Hernia and seek treatment. Medical help should always be sought before taking any other actions. </span></p>
<p class="p3" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Like this<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>article and want to read more? Check out our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/articles/">Articles</a> for quality posts covering many topics</span></p>
<p>Have a hernia? Our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/">hernia trusses</a> are made in the USA, where shipping is free!</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/">The AT Surgical Guide to Early Signs of an Inguinal Hernia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2211</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Different Types of Hernias</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 19:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>(click images to enlarge) Inguinal Hernia An inguinal hernia occurs when the structures of the groin are compromised and the intestines or bladder protrude through an&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">Different Types of Hernias</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-5694" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/types-of-hernias-and-hernia-treatment-150x300.png" alt="" width="150" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/types-of-hernias-and-hernia-treatment-150x300.png 150w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/types-of-hernias-and-hernia-treatment.png 750w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/types-of-hernias-and-hernia-treatment-600x1200.png 600w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/types-of-hernias-and-hernia-treatment-512x1024.png 512w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">(<em>click images to enlarge</em>)</p>
<h3><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Inguinal-hernia--e1483643102155.jpg" rel="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Inguinal-hernia--e1483643102155.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-2145" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Inguinal-hernia--225x300.jpg" alt="" width="194" height="259" /></a></h3>
<h3>Inguinal Hernia</h3>
<p>An inguinal hernia occurs when the structures of the groin are compromised and the intestines or bladder protrude through an abdominal wall or into an inguinal canal. This is the most common form of Hernia, &amp; over 96% of cases involve this type of Hernia.</p>
<p>This type of Hernia is most common in people with penises, due to natural weaknesses in the groin area.</p>
<h3>Incisional Hernia</h3>
<p><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Incisional-hernia-02-225x300.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-2144" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Incisional-hernia-02-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="129" height="172" /></a>If your medical history includes abdominal surgery, this hernia may be of special interest to you.</p>
<p>These most often occur to the elderly or people who are physically inactive and larger after abdominal surgery. The intestines will push through the abdominal wall where the surgery incision was made, hence the name incisional.</p>
<h3><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Femoral-hernia-02.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-2142" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Femoral-hernia-02-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="122" height="163" /></a>Femoral Hernia</h3>
<p>Are you pregnant or obese? Listen up, we’re here to warn you!</p>
<p>A femoral hernia occurs in the canal enclosing the femoral artery that brings oxygenated blood (away from your heart) to your upper thigh.</p>
<h3>Umbilical Hernia</h3>
<p><span class="s1"><b><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Umbilical-hernia-02.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-2146" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Umbilical-hernia-02-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="114" height="152" /></a></b></span>Focus in on the navel &#8211; or belly button &#8211; and you find the location of umbilical hernias.</p>
<p>This hernia occurs when sections of the small intestine compromise the abdominal wall, common in newborns, obese women, and those who have birthed many children.</p>
<h3><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Hiatus-hernia-02.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-2143" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Hiatus-hernia-02-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="166" height="222" /></a>Hiatal Hernia</h3>
<p>For the final hernia type, we’re looking at the hiatus. No not the break you want to take from work, the opening through the diaphragm that allows your esophagus to reach your tummy.</p>
<p>Your upper stomach protrudes through the opening, and you’re left with a hiatal hernia.</p>
<p class="p3" style="text-align: center;"><span class="s1">Check out our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/signs-of-inguinal-hernia/">in-depth guide to inguinal hernias</a><br />
Have a hernia? Our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/">hernia trusses</a> are made in the USA, where shipping is free!</span></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">Different Types of Hernias</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2162</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abdominal Binders, Hernia Belts, &#038; You</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AT Surgical]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 16:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At AT Surgical, we&#8217;ve been in the business of crafting belts and binders to treat various types of hernias since 1974. In this article, we&#8217;ll review our&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/">Abdominal Binders, Hernia Belts, &#038; You</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>At AT Surgical, we&#8217;ve been in the business of crafting belts and binders to treat various types of hernias since 1974. In this article, we&#8217;ll review our entire catalog of hernia-related products to help you find the best fit for your hernia.</strong></p>
<h3><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/">Left, Right, or Double Inguinal Hernia Truss</a></h3>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-5409 aligncenter" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-300x300.jpg 300w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1.jpg 1500w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-150x150.jpg 150w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-768x768.jpg 768w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/Untitled-1-100x100.jpg 100w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />AT Surgical&#8217;s Left, Right or Double Sided Inguinal/Groin Hernia Truss is made with a soft pad that applies gradual pressure and support to the weakened muscles of the groin with focused compression on the hernia. Designed to provide relief from an a reducible inguinal hernia in your right groin &#8211; post or pre-surgery. The inguinal hernia truss will provide you with the support and comfort needed to maintain your active lifestyle.</p>
<ul>
<li>Alleviates discomfort of reducible hernias</li>
<li>The Inguinal Hernia Truss is the premeire inguinal hernia support garment to provide relief from a reducible inguinal hernia in your groin – post or pre-surgery</li>
<li>Provides constant, comfortable and adjustable pressure to the hernia</li>
<li>Over-the-brief style of hernia support, worn inconspicuously under clothing – may be used while bathing or swimming</li>
<li>Easy to slip on and off</li>
<li>Measure around the waist for sizing (see Size Chart tab)</li>
<li>Made in the USA</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/" class="symple-button default blue   "" title="Visit Site" style="border-radius:3px" rel=""><span class="symple-button-inner" style="border-radius:3px">Get yours</span></a>
<h3><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels/">Universal 9″ Tall Abdominal Binder with 3 Panels</a> &amp; <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/universal-abdominal-binder-12-tall-4-panels/">Universal 12″ Tall Abdominal Binder with 4 Panels</a></h3>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-5410 aligncenter" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/219-universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels-600x600-1-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/219-universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels-600x600-1-300x300.jpg 300w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/219-universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels-600x600-1-150x150.jpg 150w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/219-universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels-600x600-1-100x100.jpg 100w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/219-universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels-600x600-1.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />The Abdominal Binder is recommended for abdominal hernia reduction, postpartum recovery, bariatric support, and flattening and slimming of the abdomen. Conforms to body contour for support and proper compression, helping to speed recovery, increase circulation and reduce pain from movement or coughing.</p>
<ul>
<li>Firmly holds dressings in proper position</li>
<li>Great for post-surgical recovery!</li>
<li>Garment stays in place &#8211; won&#8217;t roll or chafe</li>
<li>Exclusive A-T Multiple Lock Stitch and high-quality fabric</li>
<li>Soft, breathable elastic (made of nylon, polyester and Lycra) ensures comfort, durability and consistent</li>
<li>compression strength</li>
<li>Universal fit</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/universal-abdominal-binder-9-tall-3-panels/" class="symple-button default blue   "" title="Visit Site" style="border-radius:3px" rel=""><span class="symple-button-inner" style="border-radius:3px">Our 9&#8243; Hernia Binder</span></a>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/universal-abdominal-binder-12-tall-4-panels/" class="symple-button default blue   "" title="Visit Site" style="border-radius:3px" rel=""><span class="symple-button-inner" style="border-radius:3px">Our 12&#8243; Hernia Binder</span></a>
<h3 class="product_title entry-title"><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/abdominal-umbilical-hernia-belt/">Umbilical Navel Hernia Belt with Sacro Pad</a></h3>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-medium wp-image-4974 aligncenter" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H-300x300.jpg 300w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H-100x100.jpg 100w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H-150x150.jpg 150w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H-200x200.jpg 200w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/16H.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />The umbilical hernia belt/truss provides significant relief from abdominal pain associated with an umbilical hernia.</p>
<ul>
<li>Foam pad adds rigidity, padding, and provides a non-elastic zone that helps to direct compression on the hernia</li>
<li>Cotton/elastic blend provide breathable, comfortable support</li>
<li>Dual Velcro strips ensure positive closure and adjustment</li>
<li>Measure around abdomen (belly) for a proper fit. Waist (pant) size may not be a good indicator for size as most people need to wear the belt closer to the belly and not the hips. The belt is intended to fit tight and provide compression</li>
<li>Belt measures 41&#8243; L x 6&#8243; W</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/umbilical-navel-hernia-belt-w-sacro-pad/" class="symple-button default blue   "" title="Visit Site" style="border-radius:3px" rel=""><span class="symple-button-inner" style="border-radius:3px">Get Yours</span></a>
<p>Well, there you have it, hope you enjoyed! To learn more about how hernias form and how to treat them, be sure to read our article about <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/different-types-hernias/">the different types of hernia</a>.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/">Abdominal Binders, Hernia Belts, &#038; You</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/abdominal-binders-hernia-belts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2139</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 156/269 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-26 16:01:11 by W3 Total Cache
-->