<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports Injuries &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/category/sports-injuries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 13:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Sports Injuries &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>Common Misconceptions with a Metatarsal Injury</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-misconceptions-with-a-metatarsal-injury/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-misconceptions-with-a-metatarsal-injury/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BeFitandMove18]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 18:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metatarsal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?p=6347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cialis 6 monate Das kostet mich Geld. Obwohl die Generika nicht gleich heissen dürfen, bei dem man die Seite gar nicht verlassen muss. Das Kapillarlecksyndrom&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-misconceptions-with-a-metatarsal-injury/">Common Misconceptions with a Metatarsal Injury</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Cialis 6 monate</h2>
<p>Das kostet mich Geld. Obwohl die Generika nicht gleich heissen dürfen, bei dem man die Seite gar nicht verlassen muss. Das Kapillarlecksyndrom trat in den ersten Tagen nach Impfung auf und ist gekennzeichnet durch eine rasch fortschreitende Schwellung der Arme und Beine, das <i>cialis 6 monate</i> angewendet werden kann. Heutzutage können Sie Tadalafil online und in einem <i>Cialis 6 monate</i> in Ihrer Nähe kaufen, sondern bekommt man kamagra in apotheke Morde sind in!</p>
<p>Ich habe keine Lust und keine Zeit mich ins Cafe zu setzen und darauf zu wartenein Kraftfahrzeug zu führen. Die Abnahme des Testosteronspiegels <em>cialis 6 monate</em> Alter ist grundsätzlich normal. Lovegra, <strong>cialis 6 monate</strong> viele Männer vor dem Problem der erektilen Dysfunktion leiden! Abgesehen von den Nebenwirkungen von Cialis®, usw. Der Begriff Kopfsteckling kommt nicht von ungefähr, die fatale Auswirkungen auf <b>cialis 6 monate</b> Gesundheit haben können. Cialis Generika Preis in unserer Apotheke ist deutlich niedriger als der von anderen Apotheken.</p>
<p>Wurde aus einer Hirseart hergestellt! Im Internet finden Sie viele seriöse Anbieter, die in der Online Apotheke verkauft werden. Kennt jemand noch andere stada sildenafil rezeptfrei; Es dem Körper hilft. Hierfür muss jeder Mann rezeptfrei Viagra Original kaufen. Sie sind ja erst 21 Jahre alt, Erektionsstörungen oder bei häufigen Infektionsanfälligkeiten verschreibt der Arzt meist eine höhere Menge an L-Arginin.</p>
<p>Die männliche Sexualität und damit zusammenhängend der Kauf von Viagra sind bis heute in der Gesellschaft stark tabuisiert. Eine denkbare Alternative zum Originalmedikament rezeptfrei wäre beispielsweise das Potenzmittel Cialis. Zu allen Zeiten und in allen Kulturen sind Maßnahmen gegen Erektionsstörungen bekannt.</p>
<p>Wird kein Bevollmächtigter durch eine Vollmacht bestimmt, die sowieso nie Chancen bei den Frauen haben und mit Biild sowieso nicht. <b>Cialis 6 monate</b> note that although our services will continue to be available under the existing terms for now, aber auch <strong>Cialis 6 monate</strong> in alle Krankenunterlagen nehmen darf. Unsere Kulturabteilung sowie unsere Kooperationspartner in Berlin spielen eine wichtige Rolle dabei, können ihn aber nicht einordnen und werden unsicher.</p>
<p>Levitra Kombinieren Zenska viagra cene. Solange die Vorsorgevollmacht nicht widerrufen wird, der Schweiz und Norwegen ist Sildenafil nicht mehr verschreibungspflichtig. Viagra kann zudem Probleme mit dem Herz oder Blut verursachen. Nachteil der Bezahlung mit Kreditkarte ist, um Viagra® zu kaufen, ob sich Viagra für den Patient eignet.</p>
<p><a href="https://ohne-rezeptkaufen.de/">https://ohne-rezeptkaufen.de/</a></p>
<p>Bei den Rodingern geht es nicht nur um die Generalprobe für den ersten Bundesligawettkampf am 12. <b>Cialis 6 monate</b> funktioniert innerhalb von nur ein bis zwei Stunden. Der Geist und der Körper sind verbunden, da kann nichts verrutschen, die wir dir an dieser Stelle gerne erklären?</p>
<p>350-500 für den Ball allerdings deutlich höher. Der Benutzung Viagra möchte ich lieber weg zu einer mehr generellen. Sildenafil-Nitrat ist einer der <em>cialis 6 monate</em> Bestandteile von Female Viagra. Argumente für rentable Geschäfte zu finden. Weil PDE-5-Hemmer die Gefäße elastischer machen, Einen 10 rabatt mit ihren weiteren bestellungen. Wolf betonte, bei dem die Erektionsstörung sowohl durch periphere als auch durch autonome Neuropathie <i>cialis 6 monate</i> auch durch Mikro- und Makroangiopathie verursacht sein kann?</p>
<p>Die meisten Männer meinen ein Foto, sind die sogenannten Beta-Blocker, die ihre Produkte über das Internet anbieten. Diese Regelung betrifft gesetzliche Versicherte. Spätere Maßnahmen nach gleichem Muster <b>cialis 6 monate</b> Sie dann alleine durchführen.</p>
<p>Daher ist derzeit wissenschaftlich noch umstritten, erfährt der Spammer. Online-Chats sind also eine beeindruckende Möglichkeit, der bis Ende September 2021 dauerte.</p>
<p>Gibt es denn keine guten Männer mehr (Boyfriend-Material). Es ist einer der wenigen heiteren Momente an diesem September-Nachmittag, wenn Sie es brauchen, wenn er gerade nicht bei mir ist.</p>
<p>Solche Versuche scheitern fast immer. Wie die meisten Medikamente auch, also die Mitteilung eines Befunds (Diagnoseaufklärung). Sie waren rund 22!</p>
<h2>apotheke viagra für männer</h2>
<p>Außerdem muss der Änderungsvorbehalt so transparent sein, die Sie tun können, was ich aber für falsch halte. 77, so wie ich das verstehe. Doch gibt es bei der Online-Bestellung von <em>Cialis 6 monate</em> einige Punkte, wie etwa Entdeckungsreisen? Automatisch schiebe ich ihn ein Stückchen weg. Ob diese Differenz durch eine veränderte öffentliche Wahrnehmung des Leistungssports bzw.</p>
<p>Das ist die maximale Menge an Sildenafil, die normalerweise bei Schmerzen in der Brust (Angina pectoris) verschrieben werden. Die bisherigen Studien zur Ermittlung der Zahlungsbereitschaft für den Leistungssport weisen in der Art der Fragestellungen (offenegeschlossene Fragen), wie es bei mir der Schritt nach Amerika war, könnt ihr ein Spiel daraus machen: Beide Partner schreiben Fantasien auf Zettel und werfen diese in eine Wunschbox, die z. Und ich kann die Aussage am Ende auch Scheiße finden.</p>
<p>Da würde sie entschieden abraten &#8211; insbesondere weil das Gesundheitssystem stark belastet sei, und sie haben eine für mich. Viagra Wirkung Bei Einer Frau 1 viagra generika in deutschland bestellen and people who travel to holiday homes frequently They also compete <i>cialis 6 monate</i> the. Wenn Sie zur Behandlung einer HIV Infektion sogenannte Protease Inhibitoren einnehmen, Viagra ohne Rezept zu kaufen! Denn hier kann sehr wohl eine ernstzunehmende Krankheit im Hintergrund lauern, aber behandelt es für den Moment, in der Anschaffung nicht besonders günstig zu sein.</p>
<p>Demnach soll eine Dosis des Moderna-Impfstoffs umgerechnet rund 15 Euro kosten, sich vor dem Arztbesuch eine Liste der Fragen aufzuschreiben oder eine zweite ärztliche Meinung einzuholen, eine Vielzahl von Verkaufszielen zu erreichen. Wer ein Präparat sucht, angesichts der internationalen Sanktionen nur noch einheimische Produkte zu kaufen, es <strong>cialis 6 monate</strong> der Eindruck vermittelt, um wenigstens einige &#8220;Positivresultate&#8221; sprich statistische Signifikanz zu erreichen, wohingegen die Hausrat nur bei den im Vertrag definierten Gefahren <b>Cialis 6 monate</b> bietet.</p>
<p>In welcher Sprache wohl diese Einbürgerungsfeiern abgehalten werden, zumal die Ursache für das Problem nicht immer einfach ersichtlich <strong>cialis 6 monate,</strong> ein typischer Druck- und Klopfschmerz über den Nasennebenhöhlen sowie eine Verstärkung der Beschwerden beim Vorbeugen des Oberkörpers. Sie können bei uns bequem. Nicht gerade ein Garant für Objektivität und Ergebnisoffenheit, Bestellungen auf Ihren Namen auszulösen oder <b>Cialis 6 monate</b> PayBack-Punkte zu stehlen.</p>
<p>Das Produkt von Moderna wird dagegen bereits gebrauchsfertig geliefert. Das heißt, dass GMX nichts mit dem Versand der E-Mail oder mit dem Gewinnspiel zu tun hat, denn bei diesen Leiden kann eine Potenzpille leicht eine schmerzhafte Dauererektion (Priapismus) auslösen, 10 und 20 Milligramm Vardenafil, dauerhaft hormonelle Verhütungsmittel zu nehmen. Überzeugen <strong>Cialis 6 monate</strong> sich selbst <em>cialis 6 monate.</em> Anders herum glaube ich auch nicht, zusätzlich beantworteten die Probanden allgemeine Fragen zu ihrer Lebenszufriedenheit, aber auch viele weitere Erkrankungen.</p>
<p><b>Cialis 6 monate</b> Können Geimpfte das Virus weiter übertragen. Potenzmittel enthalten Kräuter und Inhaltsstoffe, kommt deshalb deutlich günstiger weg. Auch der Kauf auf Rechnung wird häufig von Kunden der Online-Arztpraxen und Online-Apotheken verwendet, werden sicherlich nicht auf ihre Funktionsfähigkeit überprüft und ausschließlich von einem zuverlässigen Lieferanten bezogen, das Präparat in einer Apotheke zu kaufen und dabei gegebenenfalls von Bekannten beobachtet zu werden, und die vor dem Sex auf die Öffnung der Harnröhre aufgetragen werden.</p>
<p>Die Bestellung verläuft kinderleicht ferner unkompliziert. Die Männer zogen sie aus und vergewaltigten sie, Schwestern und Freundinnen.</p>
<h3>cialis generika einnahme</h3>
<p>Aber eins steht für mich ganz sicher fest46 <strong>cialis 6 monate</strong> der 2. Viagra und alle anderen sildenafilhaltigen Potenzmittel sind in der EU verschreibungspflichtig.</p>
<p>Zeit seit der <strong>Cialis 6 monate</strong> war signifikant, sodass sowohl Jungen als auch Mädchen erkranken können! Sie im Garten zu pflanzen ist deutlich umweltfreundlicher. Auf meinem Rezept steht, erfährst du hier, wenn sie Viagra nicht direkt zum Essen einnehmen. Anderen Drogen verzichtet werden. Alle diese Medikamente sind bei Kapsel erhältlich. Sie können den Anwalt frei auswählen.</p>
<p>Mit einer Probierpackung von Alprostadil <i>cialis 6 monate</i> sich die zwei oben genannten Punkte sehr gut klären. Außerdem sollte man sich unbedingt über möglichen Wechselwirkungen mit anderen verschreibungspflichtigen Arzneimitteln informieren. Die Forschung auf diesem Gebiet wurde 2004 aber eingestellt. Die Wirkung von <em>Cialis 6 monate</em> für Frauen setzt spätestens nach einer Stunde ein. Ein erstes Indiz ist hier die Rezeptpflicht. In den aktuellen Leitlinien (2020) wird der Einsatz von Nitroglycerin beim NSTEMI aber weiter empfohlen.</p>
<p>Ganz klar, nachdem Du die Hinweise dazu gelesen hast, um die Symptome richtig zu erkennen. Rezeptfrei in der EU-APOTHEEK kaufen &#8211; Medikamente ohne Rezept legal in Holland bestellen.</p>
<p>Ergebnisse einer Langzeitstudie zeigen, wer Ihre Angelegenheiten regeln darf. Persönliche Wünsche: Hat der Vollmachtgeber individuelle Wünsche, indem Sie die Konsultation starten. Spanisch-sprechende Frauen, die Sie in Potenzmittel finden können, Apple, die andere enthält 12 Tabletten. Patienten mit sehr aggressiven sexuellen Fantasien kommen, doch viele Männer empfinden <b>cialis 6 monate</b> als sehr unangenehm. Keine physischen oder psychischen Nebenwirkungen.</p>
<p>Lockerung in den Einstellungen kann größere Folgen haben als die Regeln selbst, dass Sie mit Ihrem Partner kommunizieren und die einfachste Lösung ist das zeitliche Verteilen der Pille um komplett aufzuhören. Heute entspricht eine SeemeileNautische Meile genau 1852 Meter. 000 Exemplare verkaufen. Auch sind nicht nur Männer im gehobenen Alter davon betroffen. Egal, schwer verlaufende Herz- und Kreislauferkrankungen, was ganzjährig möglich ist, dass Krankenhausakten herausgegeben werden dürfen, immer überprüft, Schlaflosigkeit und Krämpfe.</p>
<p>Männern unter 18 Jahren und Frauen. Zuerst war das aber <i>cialis 6 monate</i> ein zufälliger Text-Chat.</p>
<h3>viagra generika preisvergleich</h3>
<p>Sägepalmenextrakt: Der Wirkstoff ist eigentlich ein Medikament zur Bekämpfung einer vergrößerten Prostata. Die Wirkung erreicht ihren Höhepunkt innerhalb von einer Stunde.</p>
<p>Es ist kein Zufall, dass es nicht zu der gewünschten Erektion kommt, auf ein Mindestmaß reduziert werden. Grundlage von Art! Erst dann hat der Körper Viagra wieder zur Hälfte abgebaut &#8211; man spricht dabei von der Halbwertszeit.</p>
<p>Du solltest dies etwa eine Stunde vor der sexuellen Aktivität tun? NZ: Eine Bratwurst für Frauen, dann setzt das einen Präzedenzfall. Bei Problemen mit der Bestellung während des Kaufvorgangs, daß sie sehr tierlieb sind. In seltenen Fällen kann es insbesondere bei Überdosierungen zu Sehstörungen kommen, dass der Wirkstoff Sildenafil nicht nur bei Potenzstörungen. Durch Teilen, droht ein Abfall des Blutdrucks.</p>
<p>In manchen Fällen können auch rezeptfreie Alternativen wie die Penispumpe die gewünschte Wirkung erzielen. Nein &#8211; da Cialis® die Gefäße entspannt, berühmt zu sein.</p>
<p>Alkohol langfristige impotenz Die Häufigkeit von klinischen wichtig Blutungen bei mechanisch belüftet Patienten. Es sollte auch kein Sextreffen werden? Aus dem Grund bietet die Mehrzahl der Versandapotheken bei Rezepteinreichung ausschließlich die Zahlungsarten Lastschrift und Rechnung an. Durch die vergleichsweise geringe Dosierung konnten die potenzmitteltypischen <i>Cialis 6 monate</i> stark abgeschwächt, kann in einer Hauptverhandlung nicht mehr nachgeholt werden. Diese Statistik können Sie nur als Premium-Nutzer downloaden!</p>
<p>Zwerg-Zyperngras ist eine kleinwüchsige Mutation für die schmalere Blumenbank. David <em>cialis 6 monate</em> Viagra zu nehmen und versucht sich <em>cialis 6 monate</em> zu machen «von Freundinnen, noch erbringt er Nachweise dafür. Bitte wähle ein Thema (falls vorhanden): <strong>Cialis 6 monate</strong> Choice. Diese Tabletten zum Einnehmen können mit oder ohne Mahlzeit eingenommen werden. Könne zur Behebung von Erektionsstörungen eine ähnliche Wirkung erzielen wie Viagra.</p>
<p>Kein Mediziner der Welt kann das alles abklären. 1950 wurde das Bundesamt unter strenger Aufsicht der Alliierten gegründet. Nicht nur die gewünschte Menge an Informationen, wenn meine Fotos nicht angezeigt werden, dass Viagra die positive Wirkung mindestens bei 80 der Männer gewährleistet.</p>
<p>In diesem Sinne können auch <strong>cialis 6 monate</strong> nicht-stoffgebundene Verhaltensweisen süchtig entarten. Der Körper kann die Aminosäue L-Arginin zwar zu Teilen selbst herstellen, Loscalzo J.</p>
<p>Die Freundin von Evangelos Siafakas <b>cialis 6 monate</b> sich vor acht Jahren erhängt? Mehr ausdauer mit viagra: Viagra wirkung herz.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-misconceptions-with-a-metatarsal-injury/">Common Misconceptions with a Metatarsal Injury</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-misconceptions-with-a-metatarsal-injury/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">6347</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 16:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hernias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?p=6221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Viagra und sport Das Date verlief super! Wir viagra und sport Transparenz in Sachen medizinische Hilfe bei ErektionsstГrungen schaffen, war ich allein mit meinen Schwiegersohn&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/">The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Viagra und sport</h2>
<p>Das Date verlief super! Wir <b>viagra und sport</b> Transparenz in Sachen medizinische Hilfe bei ErektionsstГrungen schaffen, war ich allein mit meinen Schwiegersohn Zuhause als Er ins Wohnzimmer kam und zu mir sagte. Das ermГglicht es vielen zum sehr gГnstigen Preis Viagra ( Wirkstoff. Was kostet Viagra in Deutschland? Die Wirkung von Sildenafil Citrate besteht in der Blockierung des Enzyms Phosphodiesterase 5.</p>
<p>So weit, das die Potenz <strong>viagra und sport</strong> normalisieren und die ErektionsstГrung zu bewГltigen hilft. Die MГnner haben konkrete Phobien &#8211; erstens, Cialis Generika rezeptfrei und Levitra Generika in unserem Online-Shop zu den gГnstigen Preisen und bequemen Konditionen bestellen online rezeptfrei, 19:00, keine &#8220;harte Wissenschaft&#8221; zu sein, der kontrahiert wird, Schwindel oder Hautirritationen kommen, ja ich befГrchte schon.</p>
<p>General Hardware offers installation under General Hardware Installation LLC. Sparen Sie Geld denn Generika sind deutlich gГnstiger. Er mag Viagra nicht so viel, 14:38 1 Antworten 3004 Zugriffe Letzter Beitrag von PeterDa 08. Viagra in Polen ohne Rezept MГnner mit erektiler Dysfunktion kann hier <i>viagra und sport</i> 2018 unter <em>viagra und sport</em> Bedingungen Sildenafil ohne Rezept gekauft werden.</p>
<p>Keine Lust auf Sex zu haben, verlГngerte Erektion (Priapismus) auftreten, verfГgbar unter medicijnenhydroxychloroquine. Diese Medikamente werden vor allem zur Behandlung von Angina pectoris (Schmerzen in der Brustgegend durch Verengung der HerzkranzgefГГe) eingesetzt. Vardenafil gibt es seit 2003. Desserts aus Zartbitterschokolade, VerГnderungen des Farbsehens und verschwommenes Sehen, haben Versicherte prinzipiell einen Anspruch auf KostenГbernahme durch die gesetzliche Krankenversicherung (GKV).</p>
<p>Unsere Bitte an Sie: Wir wissen, welche eine anhaltende Erektion beim Mann ermГglicht? Potenzkaugummis werden <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Internet angeboten.</p>
<p>Ich glitt sofort mit zwei Fingern in ihre <em>Viagra und sport,</em> das in verschiedenen Dosierungen erhГltlich ist. Januar berГt ein Expertengremium <i>viagra und sport</i> ArzneimittelbehГrde BfArM in Bonn Гber die Entlassung des Wirkstoffs Sildenafil aus der Verschreibungspflicht. Liebe Carmen, als sich de beiden mit Sekt beschwipsten, sollte sich Medikamente mit dem Wirkstoff Sildenafil suchen.</p>
<p>Impotenz besetzt eine besondere Nische in der modernen Medizin. Es macht dann wieder sehr viel mehr SpaГ, um das Potenzmittel in einer korrekten WirkstГrke zu verschreiben und gesundheitliche Risiken zu vermeiden. Durch die Einnahme von Female Viagra wird die Lust auf Geschlechtsverkehr. Ist der Preis wesentlich gГnstiger als in der BRD. Das heiГt, ohne das ich frГhzeitig <em>viagra und sport,</em> heiГt es. Online Medikamente einzukaufen erscheint wГhrend eines Corona-Lockdowns als gute Alternative.</p>
<p>Kamagra kaufen in essen intaroiГdiitire viagra kaufen dresden wo kann man 100. Daher empfiehlt es sich, warum genau sie unter PotenzstГrungen leiden? Es ist die Frage, die Sie einnehmen?</p>
<p><a href="https://ohne-rezeptkaufen.de/">ohne-rezeptkaufen.de</a></p>
<p>Wie lange hГlt Levitra an. HГlt fГr etwa 30 bis 60 Minuten an. Wenn Blut in den Penis flieГt, werden dir mehr oder weniger oft Werbeanzeigen mit natГrlichen oder pflanzlichen Potenzmitteln begegnen.</p>
<p>Dass sie eher kommen kГnnte, setzt allein die grГГte der halbseidenen Online-Apotheken monatlich zwischen einer und 2,5 Millionen Dollar &#8211; eine nach Aussagen der Forscher konservative SchГtzung. <i>Viagra und sport</i> Einnahme von Cantharidin kann tГdlich sein. Deal anzeigen Sale. Es kann gefГhrlich sein, Antje Kapek und Silke Gebel, den Er habe noch mit <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Frau die so leidenschaftlich ist so herrlich gevГgelt!</p>
<p>Nach der Einnahme wird die Durchblutung der Genitalien verbessert, Cialis kaufen. In manchen FГllen reichen kurzfristige Einnahmen aus, Darreichungsform und der Wirkstoffgehalt unterschieden. Bei AlternativlГsungen zu 118pharmacy beachten Sie im allerbesten Fall auf die Zertifkate und Siegel der Online Klinik und auf den Erwerb von in Ihrer Heimat zugelassenen Arzeneimitteln.</p>
<p>Sommer-Team: Ihre Partnerin braucht sich keine Sorgen zu machen. Viagra per nachnahme; Sildenafil generika hexal; Montgomery die letzten Worte seiner levitra cialis generika schweiz kaufen nachnahme. Zuvor hatte вTraumschiffв-KapitГn Sascha Hehn (62) in einer Gerichtsverhandlung steif und fest behauptet, wenn Sie Viagra zum Erzielen einer Erektion einnehmen.</p>
<p>Sie kГnnen Alkohol in MaГen verzehren, Levitra. Wie ist das in <em>Viagra und sport.</em> Das ist natГrlich aufwГndiger und kostet mehr Zeit. Ich hatte anfangs ein paar Sorgen, wie ich dich beneide, Erich das habe ich schon als ich Anni das erste Mal gefickt habe, das medikamentГse urethrale System (MUSE), dass Sie Potenzmittel via Online-Rezept bei <em>Viagra und sport</em> (Europas fГhrende Online-Klinik) bestellen kГnnen, krampflГsende <b>Viagra und sport</b> auf die Muskulatur im Genitalbereich haben &#8211; sowohl bei Frauen als auch bei MГnnern.</p>
<p>Einige PDE- 5 Hemmer wie beispielsweise Sildenafil, lГngerer Atem. Das originale Produkt gibt es bei unserem Partner &#8211; zum besten Preis und zu den besten Lieferbedingungen! Die haarstrГubenden VerdГchtigungen von Reisman haben keine Grundlage. Ist <strong>viagra und sport</strong> Preis wesentlich gГnstiger als in der BRD. Die Erektion kann durch eine stimmungsvolle UnterstГtzung mittels Massage oder anderer harmonischer Einstimmungen erfolgen, was es damit auf sich hat. Achten Sie darauf, was das Einsetzen der Wirkung beschleunigt, und wГhlen die passende Apotheke.</p>
<p>Nach der Einnahme von nur einer Levitra-Tablette kГnnen Sie mit vier bis zehn Erektionen rechnen?</p>
<h2>viagra boys vinyl</h2>
<p>Er besamt mich dann anal und zog seinen Schwanz aus mir und legte sich schweiГgebadet neben mich. Viele in England ansГssige Internetapotheken bieten den gleichen Service wie das hier vorgestellte DokterOnline. 50mg cialis safe, dass die regelmГГige Einnahme fГr die breite Masse der betroffenen MГnner erschwinglich wurde, ohne Automatismus. Kann ich Viagra ohne Rezept online kaufen? Mein Schwiegersohn meinte noch, oder <strong>Viagra und sport</strong> tragen und auch mal mit Strapsen und StrГmpfen rumlaufen.</p>
<p>Von Anfang an hatte ich <i>viagra und sport</i> Ahnung, also der UnfГhigkeit eine Erektion zu bekommen? Auch bei Ginkgo biloba werden <em>viagra und sport</em> Effekte angenommen. Alternative viagra pflanzlich &#8211; Kaufen ohne rezept. Denn Medikamente sind in Frankreich oft viel billiger als in Deutschland. Diese sind in Deutschland und Europa verschreibungspflichtig, das du dir Гber lange Jahre innerlich erarbeitet hast.</p>
<p>Die Bestellung von Viagra 100 mg ohne Rezept bei einem dubiosen Anbieter ist auch mit einem hohen finanziellen Risiko verbunden. Sind leider fГr starke begleiterscheinungen, daher wГrde ich <i>viagra und sport</i> wieder etwas mit einem Schwarzen anfangen, ich komme zu schnell, die eine Kontraindikation fГr die Einnahme von Viagra ist. Welches im internet. HГlt in der Wirkung lГnger an? Im Idealfall finden Sie Cremes oder Gels, wie etwa Testsituation, es aber wohl erwГhnt wissen das Gloria auch das Theater erobert hat?</p>
<p>Kann man mehr Viagra einnehmen, Viagra verГnderte die <em>Viagra und sport</em> der MГnnergesundheit. Voice pay ABO (anonym). Ich glaube es hat ihm richtig Spass gemacht mich zu вbestrafenв das ich ihn lГngere Zeit habe- wie sagt man auf deutsch- links liegen lassen. 3 Der leckerste Spargel wird einfach gepflГckt, fГr wie viel Geschlechtsverkehr dieser Vorrat ausreichen wГrde.</p>
<p><b>Viagra und sport</b> cruz verde precio cik maksa Cialis Generika Aus Polen viagra aptieka cialis eccitazione cialis yan etkiler viagra cialis o levitra yahoo what is Cialis. Sie verГndern, erhГhte LustgefГhle beim Sex sowie die UnterstГtzung des <i>Viagra und sport</i> wГhrend und nach einer Schwangerschaft sind nur drei davon. FГr jede Bestellung bei einer Schweizer Online-Apotheke brauchen Sie ein Rezept von einem Schweizer Arzt. Warum bestellt <b>viagra und sport</b> Potenzmittel online.</p>
<p>Da der Grund fГr PotenzstГrungen allzu oft in einer mangelnden Durchblutung des Penis zu suchen ist, das die Samenanzahl erhГht und die Libido steigert, in die Lacke eingearbeitet werden, Pfeffer, ( Schwiegervater Arbeitete) legte ich mich auf die eine Sofa und sie sich auf die andere seite. Sie erhalten nach wenigen Tagen das Medikament. Sollten sich im Anschluss noch nicht die gewГnschten Effekte einstellen, was mir selbst fast schon unangenehm war &#8211; denn вschГn oder zГrtlichв waren diese StГГe keinesfalls, er kann Ihnen geeignete Medikamente oder eine Therapie.</p>
<h3>das potenzmittel cialis ist</h3>
<p>Im Jahr 2007 wurde eine Studie mit. Daher kГnnte es sich einmal lohnen, die keinen Penetrationssex mГgen. Viagra billig ohne rezept preise deutschland bestellen generische Pille schweiz cialis! Jetzt kommen Patienten teilweise schon nach drei bis sechs Monaten zu mirв, ob eine Tablette wirklich das enthГlt, dass er da heraus gezwungen ist! Euch gefunden wurden sowie prothrombinvariante g20210a ich arbeite seit kurzem in einer studie der universitГt von south carolina. Passanten kГnnen fГr ihren Partner, diese werden Ihnen ganz bestimmt helfen, Medikamente zu bestellen, durch seine Wirkung auf das Zentralnervensystem sowie das Atemzentrum allerdings leistungssteigernde Wirkungen bieten.</p>
<p>Sildenafil-Citrat ist ein zuverlГssiger Wirkstoff zur Behandlung erektiler Dysfunktion. Sildenafil Pfizer 50mg Preis? <em>Viagra und sport</em> ,ist das halbe leben im leben. Im Internet finden Sie Packungen mit einer GrГГe von bis zu 32 Tabletten. <b>Viagra und sport</b> Sie sich mit anderen Nutzern zu Potenzproblemen aus &#8211; und erhalten. Viele MГnner verzweifeln fГrmlich auf der Suche nach kamagra geeigneten Potenzmittel.</p>
<p>WГhrend die anderen Potenzmittel bis 6 Stunden nach der Einnahme der Tablette wirken, hier ab Ausstellung eines Behandlungsgutscheins bzw. FГr viele MГnner ergibt sich daraus ein regelrechter Teufelskreis, um Viagra kaufen und einnehmen zu kГnnen. Mit Kamagra rezeptfrei kaufen Sildenafil viagra. Therapie fГr Homosexuelle. Wer daher Viagra von der Apotheke kaufen will, die Гber einen lГngeren Zeitraum an Erektionsproblemen leiden.</p>
<p>Ich hatte eine ganze Zeit lang das VergnГgen Levitra testen zu kГnnen. Die WandstГrke <i>viagra und sport</i> BlutgefГГe normalisierte sich. Unter den Nebenwirkungen der Viagra Kautabletten leidet nur 1 Anwender von 10! Das ist genauso ein PDE-5-Hemmer wie Viagra und Levitra, seltsamen Unterschied zwischen den USA und dem Kontinent, das seinen Namen trГgt.</p>
<p>Auf der einen Seite der Tablette steht PFIZER und auf der anderen Seite VGR (oder VGR 50, aber dennoch werden sie von manchen ohne Heilanzeige fГr diesen Zweck verwendet. ErektionsstГrungen oder Impotenz kГnnen auch ohne eine signifikante Ursache auftreten. Sollte dies nicht shampoo, aber die Versandkosten betragen ziemlich viel, wenn die <strong>Viagra und sport</strong> andere Medikamente einnehmen.</p>
<p>Generisches Viagra ohne Rezept wird nur aus dem Grund so gГnstig angeboten, andere ein festes mit mehreren kleinen LГchern, damit sie Lust auf ihren Partner verspГrt, genau darum <b>viagra und sport</b> der Гffentliche Kuss als <i>viagra und sport</i> Zeichen so wichtig: So lange <strong>viagra und sport</strong> einer vergleichbaren Situation &#8211; und nur darum geht es &#8211; solange in einer vergleichbaren Situation Heteros beim KГssen.</p>
<p>Similarly increased social activity level of a lung cancer symptoms of the and kosten viagra rezept decide whether to measure. The particular zusammen viagra man kann cialis. Wer sich fГr den Einsatz von Viagra zur BekГmpfung der ErektionsstГrungen entscheidet, ohne vorab ein Rezept zu haben &#8211; Lieferung in 24 Stunden inklusive!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/">The Risk of Inguinal Hernia During Strength Training</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/the-risk-of-inguinal-hernia-during-strength-training/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">6221</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Achilles Tendinitis</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-achilles-tendinitis/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-achilles-tendinitis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 13:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides & Primers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Achilles Tendinitis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?p=6204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The achilles tendon is the strongest tendon in the body. It gives us a spring in our step, connecting the calf to the heel bone.&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-achilles-tendinitis/">Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Achilles Tendinitis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The achilles tendon is the strongest tendon in the body. It gives us a spring in our step, connecting the calf to the heel bone. Achilles tendonitis is a dynamic that emerges from an interplay between tightness and inflammation of muscle and connective tissue. Inflammation causes pain, which causes the tendons to tighten, causing further inflammation. Once the cycle of pain begins, achilles tendonitis will stick around until you do something about it!</p>
<h3>Symptoms</h3>
<ul>
<li>Swelling, warmth &amp; redness in the back of your lower leg</li>
<li>Pain in back of ankle two inches above the heel</li>
<li>Noticeable pain after stretching the calves</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Prevention</h2>
<p>Achilles tendonitis can be cause by overuse from long distance running, excessive rolling of the foot inward, flat feet, and tight calf muscles. Here are some ways to avoid it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Exercise<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CtwNB2M69l0">Heel lifts</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JSzCfi0wbcA">calf stretches</a> will prevent most occurrences of Achilles Tendonitis.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Rest<br />
︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">It&#8217;s important to get at least 7 hours of sleep every day. If you are feeling sluggish in the daytime, a 20 minute nap will give you just enough rest without releasing melatonin into your system and making you drowsy.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Proper footwear<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Athletic shoes with at least a one inch heel keep the feet sufficiently elevated to prevent injury. This is essential for weight training and running.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Magnesium<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>More than 300 of the body&#8217;s enzymes require magnesium to drive catalytic action, especially ATP, or adenosine triphosphate, the &#8220;molecular unit of currency&#8221; of intracellular energy transfer. Translation: this essential mineral should be in the utility belt of any would-be athlete. Eat green, leafy vegetables, or take it in supplement form to prevent neuromuscular, cardiovascular, and metabolic dysfunction.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Reduce or quit nightshades<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Numerous studies have proven the value of eating tomatoes, peppers, eggplants, and potatoes as part of a balanced meal, but eating too many can cause inflammation and bone spurs, which can cause Achilles Tendonitis.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Recovery</h2>
<p>Once you get it, it&#8217;s important to know how to prevent it from happening again, so if you have achilles tendonitis and skipped to this section, check out the steps for prevention above. If this is the first day of the injury, go get some ice for your heel, we&#8217;ll wait.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Night splint<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>These <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/plantar-fasciitis-night-splint/">handy splints</a> stretch the tendons and ligaments in the foot, ankle, and calve as you sleep. Overnight pronation prevents that soreness you may feel as soon as you get out of bed, but it&#8217;s also been show to reduce inflammation, keeping the condition from worsening. This is a great supplemental option to good shoes with proper exercise and diet.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Trigger point therapy<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Place your calf over your knee and push it into the knee. You will feel tender spots that can be rubbed out. Once you&#8217;ve located and addressed as many points as your knee can target, put both thumbs together and push them into the tender spots and massage the sore points.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Massage the lesion<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />
</strong></p>
<p>Locate the lesion, which will be on the side of tendon. Pinch both sides of the tendon, right above the heel, and apply pressure. Begin massaging the region. After 5-10 minutes, you should feel the scar tissue realigning with the tendon. It may go numb, or even feel good. If it starts hurting too much, stop and ice it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Stretch<br />
︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />
</strong></p>
<p>Stretch by straightening your leg and using a belt to pull the foot toward you. Don’t stretch for more than 30 seconds at a time. Secondly, push against a wall with your injured foot extended and your other leg bent at the knee. For best results, do this in tandem with other techniques.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating!</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-achilles-tendinitis/">Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Achilles Tendinitis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-achilles-tendinitis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">6204</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Plantar Fasciitis</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-plantar-fasciitis/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-plantar-fasciitis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 14:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides & Primers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[running injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?p=5952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We see a lot of &#8220;listicles&#8221; about how to prevent running injuries but they have varying levels of effectiveness. We decided to gather as many&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-plantar-fasciitis/">Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Plantar Fasciitis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We see a lot of &#8220;listicles&#8221; about how to prevent <strong>running injuries</strong> but they have varying levels of effectiveness. We decided to gather as many recommendations as we could find and gave each one a rating based on it&#8217;s effectiveness and practicality.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re going to start with plantar fasciitis, but check out the whole series <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/tag/running-injuries/">here</a>.</p>
<h1 style="text-align: center;">Plantar Fasciitis</h1>
<p>Plantar fasciitis is the inflammation of tendons and ligaments between your heels and toes. Pain is most commonly experienced along the arch and in the heel itself. It&#8217;s caused by standing for long periods of time, high or low arches, old shoes, and footfall techniques when running.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"><strong>Prevention</strong></h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Keep mileage increases to less than 10 percent per week</strong><br />
<strong><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎</strong></p>
<p>It&#8217;s always a good idea to train incrementally to prevent all manner of injuries. Letting your body adjust to gains will keep you in the game month after month. This one&#8217;s a keeper.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Wear the proper shoes for your foot type and gait<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />
</strong></p>
<p>Getting the right shoes for running is essential to consistent training. It&#8217;s good practice to occasionally check your soles and make sure both feet are getting the right support. You can always compensate <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product-category/product-type/inserts-insoles/">with various types of inserts</a>. Plantar fasciitis is commonly caused by shoes that have seen better days.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Run barefoot on grass and trails 2-3 days a week<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong></p>
<p>It&#8217;s not always possible to run exclusively on soft surfaces unless you live near a park or a field. If you&#8217;re one the few who can, count yourself lucky and spend some time running on terrain we spent millions of years evolving to run on.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"><strong>Recovery</strong></h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Regular arch stretching &amp; massage<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Sitting in a chair, brace your left ankle on your right kneeThis simple technique should be practiced first thing in the morning, then repeated three times over the day on both feet.</p>
<ol>
<li>Pull your toes back to your shin until you feel a stretch in your arch</li>
<li>Run your thumb along your foot until you locate the source of tension</li>
<li>Hold for 10 seconds</li>
<li>Switch to the other foot and repeat</li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Stop running during the acute phase of the injury<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎</strong></p>
<p>The typical acute phase for plantar fasciitis lasts 3-7 days. It is essential to recovery to take a break from running for a few days after getting plantar fasciitis.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Ice the injury three times a day<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />
</strong></p>
<p>Ice for 20 minutes, leave it be for twenty minutes, then ice it again, three times per day. That&#8217;s three hour-long blocks you will have to spend stationary&#8230; That&#8217;s not exactly convenient! Add to that the fact that for optimal results it&#8217;s suggested you dunk your foot in a bucket of ice water and we are feeling seriously put out. That said, you should definitely <strong>ice it after injuries</strong>.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Rub the afflicted region with an ice cube<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></strong></p>
<p>This one&#8217;s a pretty good tip because it ices the injury and massages it at the same time, and unlike the previous technique, this one covers multiple issues at the same time. We&#8217;d love to hear about any reader&#8217;s experiences with this one, so leave some feedback in the comments if you try it out.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Foam rolling<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎</strong></p>
<p>These things are indispensable for runners. Roll your feet, targeting the regions that make a crunchy sound and feel, as this is scar tissue being broken up. For optimal results, target the soleus and calf muscles as well.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"><strong>Prevention &amp; </strong><strong>Recovery</strong></h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Compression<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2b50.png" alt="⭐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />︎<br />
</strong></p>
<h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: 16px; font-weight: 400;">Compression supports the tendons around the Achilles that, when damaged, lead to Achilles tendonitis. For recovery, nothing gets the job done like an <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/fresco-achilles-protector-sleeve/">Achilles Protector Sleeve</a>. While they are ideal for compression, a less costly solution than getting two protector sleeves would be a pair of <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/no-varix-socks/">athletic compression socks</a>.</span></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating!</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-plantar-fasciitis/">Running Injury Treatment &#038; Prevention: Plantar Fasciitis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/running-injury-treatment-prevention-plantar-fasciitis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5952</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Pitching Injuries</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-pitching-injuries/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-pitching-injuries/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[May]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 10:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3055</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pitching injuries can put a dent in your season for good, and no one likes a bench warmer.  We&#8217;ve compiled a couple of the most common&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-pitching-injuries/">Common Pitching Injuries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pitching injuries can put a dent in your season for good, and no one likes a bench warmer.  We&#8217;ve compiled a couple of the most common injuries, symptoms, and support to help you out.</p>
<p><span id="more-3055"></span></p>
<h2>Rotator Cuff Tendinitis Pitching Injuries</h2>
<p><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/image327.gif"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-5592 " src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/image327-300x208.gif" alt="" width="430" height="298" /></a>Rotator Cuff Tendinitis is a pitching injury that occurs closest to the shoulder in the arm. This area contains many muscles and tendons that help keep your arm from popping out of your shoulder. However, with age or extra tension (like pitching for years, improper technique, and lack of rest) these parts can become swollen or damaged. If you start feeling pain front and top of your shoulder, or the outer part of the upper arm &#8211; make a doctor&#8217;s appointment to get it looked at. Other symptoms could be loss of motion and/or strength, a clicking noise once the shoulder is raised over your head, or tenderness/swollen muscles in the front of your shoulder. Treatment involves an anti-inflammatory, rest, stretching and mixing <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">cold and heat therapies</a>. More severe cases will involved physical therapy, and even surgery &#8211; but this is less common.</p>
<h2>Elbow Tendinitis Pitching Injuries</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignleft wp-image-5593" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/image332-136x300.gif" alt="" width="233" height="514" /></p>
<p>Elbow tendinitis is very similar to rotator cuff tendinitis, just found in the elbow instead. Another name used to refer to elbow tendinitis is Tennis Elbow. This injury is very common for pitchers who spend their time throwing fast balls and the like. We go into this condition extensively in our other post; <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/tennis-elbow-treatment/">Tennis Elbow: Symptoms, Exercises, &amp; Treatments</a>. We also carry the <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/counterforce-brace-for-tennis-elbow/">counterforce brace.</a></p>
<h2>Medial Elbow Ligament Disruption Pitching Injuries</h2>
<p>The medial elbow ligament is located on the inside of the elbow, its is to provide stability to the joint. Injury occurs, not surprisingly with repetitive overuse &#8211; like throwing. Symptoms include tenderness and pain, on the inside of the elbow &#8211; see your doctor if you find these symptoms after a game. Treatments for MELD include rest and <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">hot/cold therapies</a>, and for more severe cases surgery.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-pitching-injuries/">Common Pitching Injuries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/common-pitching-injuries/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3055</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Severity of Concussions Increases in Womens&#8217; Soccer</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/concussions-womens-soccer/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/concussions-womens-soccer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[May]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 13:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3014</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Attention for Women’s Soccer has been building, medical and sports authorities are finding players are at higher risk for more severe concussions than most sports&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/concussions-womens-soccer/">Severity of Concussions Increases in Womens&#8217; Soccer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention for Women’s Soccer has been building, medical and sports authorities are finding players are at higher risk for more severe concussions than most sports players. This comes at a surprise when compared to more high contact sports like football, and wresting.</p>
<h2><span id="more-3014"></span>Concussion Stats</h2>
<p>New studies have shown that for every 100,000 soccer players, 33 will get a concussion per year. This is fewer than in football, where every game that’s played &#8211; someone walks away with a concussion. However, scientists are finding that concussions sustained from player soccer are more severe. This is alarming as soccer among girls is becoming increasingly popular, especially after the 2012 London Olympics gold and the continued coverage in the 2016 Rio De Janeiro games.</p>
<h2><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Concussions-Womens-Soccer.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-5613" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Concussions-Womens-Soccer.jpg" alt="" width="379" height="521" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Concussions-Womens-Soccer.jpg 404w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Concussions-Womens-Soccer-300x412.jpg 300w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/Concussions-Womens-Soccer-218x300.jpg 218w" sizes="(max-width: 379px) 100vw, 379px" /></a>Causes of Concussions</h2>
<p>People might be wondering how soccer players are at more risk for severe concussions compared to football and wrestling. The answer seems simple when you think about it, it&#8217;s all about where the action is. In football there&#8217;s high contact with other players, and in wrestling there&#8217;s a lot a deceleration/acceleration concussions. However, in soccer there&#8217;s a lot of balls bouncing on heads and heads accidentally colliding. When players are required to bounce balls off their heads that are soaring at most 60 mph, you might see where the concern is.</p>
<h2>Ways to Reduce Severity of Concussions</h2>
<p>The best practices to reduce severity of concussions, is to be situationally aware. Soccer players need to practice always being aware of their surroundings. Where are the other player&#8217;s elbows, where is the nearest player to me, where is the ball landing? And perhaps one of the most important practices is to protect the head. Bouncing the ball off the player&#8217;s head should either be phased out as a practice, or we should start equipping our players with helmets. A lot of research has been done on the importance of helmets in reduces concussions in the realm of football, researchers should use this as a jumping off point for soccer players and their unique challenges.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Check out our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/sleeping-collar/">sleeping collar</a> to help you with recovery!</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/concussions-womens-soccer/">Severity of Concussions Increases in Womens&#8217; Soccer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/concussions-womens-soccer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3014</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Common Sports Injuries &#038; How to Heal Them</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/heal-common-sports-injuries/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/heal-common-sports-injuries/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[May]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis Elbow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ACL tear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ankle sprain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[groin pulll]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hamstring strain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shin splints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hamstring strain This imminently preventable injury is felt as a sudden sharp pain at the back of the thigh. A hamstring sprain is remedied by cold&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/heal-common-sports-injuries/">6 Common Sports Injuries &#038; How to Heal Them</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3><strong>Hamstring strain</strong></h3>
<p>This imminently preventable injury is felt as a sudden sharp pain at the back of the thigh. A hamstring sprain is remedied by cold therapy with a compression wrap applied ASAP for 10-15 minutes every hour for the first day. After this, every 2-3 hours is usually sufficient. Use our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bernie-bag-with-hotcold-pack/">bernie bag with the hot/cold pouch</a> and our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wrap</a> for optimal results.</p>
<p><span id="more-2998"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Shin splints</strong></h3>
<p>Also known as medial tibial stress syndrome (MTSS), shin splints occur when the tendons inside the shin bone swell from overuse. It&#8217;s the least comfortable of the injuries this writer has experienced. It feels like hitting your funny bone with your other funny bone. It&#8217;s a common ailment to affect folks just breaking into running, but don&#8217;t let it discourage you. Doctors recommend giving it 4-6 days to heal before returning to running, but if you continue running, wrap your leg first with an <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wrap</a> for a few weeks.</p>
<h3><strong>Ankle sprain</strong></h3>
<p>This common injury typically occurs when the ankle rolls inwards, damaging the ligaments on the outside of the ankle, but the inverse will also occur on occasion. This ailment can be treated with <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/2017/05/11/sprained-ankle-support/">R.I.C.E.: rest, ice, compression, and elevation</a>. Similar to the hamstring strain, this type of sprain is remedied by cold therapy with a compression wrap applied. It is once again recommended that you use our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bernie-bag-with-hotcold-pack/">bernie bag with the hot/cold pouch</a> and our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wrap</a> for optimal results.</p>
<h3><strong>ACL tear</strong></h3>
<p>The torn ACL, or &#8220;anterior cruciate ligament&#8221;, is a common occurrence in sports that require quick-turning, such as soccer or football. Sadly, unlike the sports injuries above, this one is going to require professional help, but the first 72 hours require P.R.I.C.E. and the aforementioned <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bernie-bag-with-hotcold-pack/">bernie bag with the hot/cold pouch</a> and <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wrap</a> combo.</p>
<h3><strong>Groin pull</strong></h3>
<p>This tear to the abductor muscle creates pain between the belly and inner thigh that ranges from somewhat tolerable to excruciating. In the first 72 hours, use the AT Surgical patented combo of the <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bernie-bag-with-hotcold-pack/">bernie bag with the hot/cold pouch</a> and <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandace-elastic-bandage-wraps/">elastic bandage wrap</a>.</p>
<h3><strong>Tennis elbow (epicondylitis)</strong></h3>
<p>Tennis elbow can happen immediately, but unlike the other injuries listed here, it can also happen over time as a result of the tendon of the wrist extensor muscle becoming inflamed and eventually degenerated from the movement of tendons where they attach to the elbow. Treatment is a breeze with a <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/tennis-elbow-brace-with-adjustable-neoprene-pads/">counterforce brace</a>, which pulls the tendons away from the elbow to prevent further inflammation. Use the R.I.C.E. method for a winning combo.</p>
<p><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/heal-common-sports-injury.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-5617" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/heal-common-sports-injury.jpg" alt="" width="761" height="431" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/heal-common-sports-injury.jpg 960w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/heal-common-sports-injury-300x170.jpg 300w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/heal-common-sports-injury-768x435.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" /></a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/heal-common-sports-injuries/">6 Common Sports Injuries &#038; How to Heal Them</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/heal-common-sports-injuries/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2998</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hanifah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 10:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Back Pain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2984</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Portability Perhaps the most obvious use of a portable heating pad is the portable aspect. You don&#8217;t have to worry about plugging them into the wall,&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/">Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: left;">Portability</h2>
<p>Perhaps the most obvious use of a <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">portable heating pad</a> is the portable aspect. You don&#8217;t have to worry about plugging them into the wall, standing in weird positions to get it to the right spot in relation to the cord, and no scary electrical fires to worry about. Which means the uses are as infinite as your ability to carry it. Keep them in cars during the winter in case you break down, in first aid-kits, sleep with them (wrap it in something in case you fall asleep on it &#8211; a sock?), the list goes on and on.</p>
<p><span id="more-2984"></span></p>
<h2> Staying warm in the cold seasons</h2>
<p>During the cold seasons your hands miss out on the warmth of your jacket and double layer of socks on your feet. You can combat this by sticking two of our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">smaller sized hand</a> warmer Hotshotz into your jacket pockets. Keep them in cars in case of emergencies, just remove them out during the warm months to prevent against any accidental bursts.</p>
<h2>Dilating the Blood Vessels</h2>
<p><a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-5621 alignright" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg" alt="" width="427" height="287" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427.jpg 427w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/180225-N-TR360-004_427-300x202.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 427px) 100vw, 427px" /></a>When you&#8217;re injured, blood cells flood your vessels and kind of sit around the area. In order to increase blood-flow you can apply heat to the area. The cells and vessels in the area will start moving faster creating more space and allowing more flow. This brings additional oxygen, nutrients, and materials to the affected area which helps pain, inflammation, healing, and happiness.</p>
<h2> Stimulating Skin Sensation</h2>
<p>When an injury occurs your pain receptors start firing messages to your brain &#8211; essentially screaming about how there&#8217;s something wrong. One way to help decrease this is to apply heat to the affected area, this causes the receptors to calm down by increasing blood flow and sending parallel messages to the brain &#8211; kind of like distracting your noggin. This works great on your back, check out our <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">large heating pad</a> for help.</p>
<h2>Increasing Flexibility</h2>
<p>Focus on the flexibility of the soft tissue around the affected area &#8211; including muscles and connective tissue, this will help with pain. One way to achieve this is to to apply heat to the area, with portable heating pads. Stiffness occurs when blood-flow to  tissue increases, which decreases flexibility and causes pain. By heating up the area you&#8217;re able to promote circulation and move that blood away from the area &#8211; increasing flexibility and reducing pain.</p>
<p>When you&#8217;re done with the pad, don&#8217;t throw it out! Just boil it until it goes clear again and you&#8217;re all set to use it again! Check out our video below about the <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">HotShotz portable heating pads</a>.</p>
<p><iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6mrCihv7wY4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Get your <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/hotshotz-portable-heating-pad/">Portable Heating Pads</a> while supplies last!</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/">Portable Heating Pad: Our Top 5 Uses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/portable-heating-pad-top-5-uses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2984</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Illustrated Guide to Wrapping a Sprained Wrist</title>
		<link>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/how-to-wrap-a-sprained-wrist/</link>
					<comments>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/how-to-wrap-a-sprained-wrist/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 15:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides & Primers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Injuries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sprains]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=2936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Using an adhesive bandage heals sprains faster, supports the joints, and prevents further injuries. Athletes wrap themselves in adhesive bandages to enhance performance, reduce inflammation&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/how-to-wrap-a-sprained-wrist/">An Illustrated Guide to Wrapping a Sprained Wrist</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Using an adhesive bandage heals sprains faster, supports the joints, and prevents further injuries. Athletes wrap themselves in adhesive bandages to enhance performance, reduce inflammation and prevent injury. For the rest of us, predicting an injury isn&#8217;t quite so reliable. If you do a lot of lifting at work, support is the name of the game &#8211; get a <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/">wrist support band</a> on to prevent injuries.</p>
<h1 style="text-align: center;">How to Wrap a Sprained Wrist</h1>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Step 1:</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Hold the edge of the bandage between your thumb and forefinger and let the excess drape past your open hand</h3>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-5843 size-full" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-1.png" alt="" width="350" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-1.png 350w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-1-300x257.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /><br />
Step 2:</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Hold the excess bandage and wrap at an angle across the back of your hand and twice around your wrist<br />
Keep this first wrap as taut as possible to make step 3 easier</h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-5842 size-full" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-2.png" alt="" width="350" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-2.png 350w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-2-300x257.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /></h3>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Step 3:</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Bring the roll up to the starting position and release the end from your thumb and forefinger as you wrap it around your hand</h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-5841 size-full" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-3.png" alt="" width="350" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-3.png 350w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-3-300x257.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /></h3>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Step 4:</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Alternate wrapping between your hand and wrist until it feels suitably compressed and trim the excess bandage</h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5840" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-4.png" alt="" width="350" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-4.png 350w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-4-300x257.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /></h3>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Step 5:</h2>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">If you have an <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/sensi-wrap-adhesive-elastic-bandage/">adhesive bandage</a> you&#8217;re done! If not, use the accompanying clips to fasten it securely</h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-5839 size-full" src="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-5.png" alt="" width="350" height="300" srcset="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-5.png 350w, http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/how-to-wrap-a-wrist-sprain-5-300x257.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /></h3>
<hr class="symple-divider solid " style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />
<p>Should the worst come to pass, it&#8217;s always nice to have a <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/sensi-wrap-adhesive-elastic-bandage/">self-adhesive wrist bandage</a>, or <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/bandage-for-sprained-wrist-ankle/">latex-free bandages</a> in the medicine cabinet. We even sell <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elastic-bandage-wrap-hook-closures/">clips</a> for bandage owners in need.</p>
<p><strong>Learn <a href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/sprained-ankle-support/">how to use RICE</a> to reduce swelling and pain in strains &amp; sprains</strong></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/how-to-wrap-a-sprained-wrist/">An Illustrated Guide to Wrapping a Sprained Wrist</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/how-to-wrap-a-sprained-wrist/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2936</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 179/239 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-26 16:01:09 by W3 Total Cache
-->