<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Best Sellers &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product-category/best_sellers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 12:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Best Sellers &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>Ankle Support</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/ankle-support/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/ankle-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 17:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=1013</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lessen muscle fatigue and achieve better performance results by helping to increase circulation to the lower extremities. Wear it all day, wear it during sports activities, or when you travel. Comfortable soothing compression directly aids better blood circulation and therefore the amount of oxygen that can travel to your muscles while you work out.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/ankle-support/">Ankle Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seamless design maximizes comfort and removes pressure points on the heel and back of the ankle. Soft elastic nylon/spandex material provides support and relief from the arch of the foot to the leg.</p>
<ul>
<li>20 &#8211; 30 mmHg &#8211; Firm Compression</li>
<li>Made with an open toe and reinforced heel.</li>
<li>Smooth, opaque fabric.</li>
<li>Available in White and Beige.</li>
<li>Sold individually.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/ankle-support/">Ankle Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/ankle-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1013</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reflex Wrist Support Healthgenie for Symptoms of Carpal Tunnel Syndrome</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/wrist-support/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/wrist-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 20:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=978</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This popular wrist brace helps provide comfortable relief from repetitive motion discomforts and helps stabilize post-surgery and post-cast situations. The range of motion is restricted,&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/wrist-support/">Reflex Wrist Support Healthgenie for Symptoms of Carpal Tunnel Syndrome</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This popular wrist brace helps provide comfortable relief from repetitive motion discomforts and helps stabilize post-surgery and post-cast situations. The range of motion is restricted, but not eliminated. The Reflex Wrist Brace features an open palm design with an adjustable thumb strap for comfort. The molded reflex pad eliminates the need for metal stays and helps provide an element of safety when working in electrical situations. Tension strap provides added compression.</p>
<p>The wrist braces have a protective role in activities where wrists require an extraordinary effort like weight lifting or bodybuilding. In these cases, using pressure around the wrist may prevent sprains and strains.<br />
Finally, they are used in sports which force the wrist play, like those played with a paddle or racket (tennis, paddle, badminton) or hockey. Sometimes they have a double purpose: protect the wrist from injuries and wipe the sweat from the forehead. For this purpose, they are made in absorbent materials such as cotton or plush</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>One size fits most</li>
<li>Ligament Strain</li>
<li>Bone hyperplasia</li>
<li>Restoration of health</li>
<li>Daily protection</li>
<li>Keep warm</li>
<li>Aids in the healing of injured wrists</li>
<li>Made of powerful elastic for total support</li>
<li>Ideal for work or sports</li>
<li>Easily adjusted for maximum convenience</li>
<li>Support strap provides secure positioning</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Type: Adjustable Stabilising</li>
<li>Item Type: Body Shaper</li>
<li>Style: BodySuits</li>
<li>Material: Elastic</li>
<li>Size Type: Regular</li>
<li>Gender: Men/Women</li>
<li>Rise Type: High-Rise</li>
<li>Features: Skin-Friendly</li>
<li>Color: Different Colors</li>
</ul>
<h3>Size:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Size available</li>
<li>Small, medium, large, Xlarge &amp; 2Xlarge</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/wrist-support/">Reflex Wrist Support Healthgenie for Symptoms of Carpal Tunnel Syndrome</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/wrist-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">978</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elbow Cap, Healthgenie Compression Stabilizer, Adjustable And Pain Relief Support</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elbow-cap/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elbow-cap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 14:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=971</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The AT 20 Elbow Cap has been manufactured under the guidance of professionals at AT Surgical so that we can offer our clients with the very&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elbow-cap/">Elbow Cap, Healthgenie Compression Stabilizer, Adjustable And Pain Relief Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The AT 20 Elbow Cap has been manufactured under the guidance of professionals at AT Surgical so that we can offer our clients with the very best. The Elbow Cap is efficiently designed and manufactured by our professionals using top quality raw material and highly developed technology.</p>
<p>It is designed as such that it applies stable pressure across your elbow joint, which provides ultimate pain relief from a variety of ailments including tendonitis, joint inflammation, tennis elbow, golf elbow, and other elbow pain.</p>
<p>With AT 20 Elbow Cap you’ll be able to tackle any activity life throws your way while ensuring you’re a step ahead in injury prevention.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>The Elbow Cap is manufactured to provide superior support, comfort, and relief without you having to compromise on your mobility.</li>
<li>This is made of a material that is tight, form-fitting, and breathable compression. Thus maintaining joint stability regardless of activity, helping improve blood circulation and ease the pain while avoiding the itchiness common to neoprene supports.</li>
<li>Professionals at AT Surgical has taken the time to develop a specialized fabric blend for the AT 20 Elbow Cap offering all-around superior protection and support above and beyond what you’ve experienced before.</li>
<li>Though the AT 20 Elbow Cap has been designed and manufactured to aid pain relief, our Elbow supports are also the perfect fit for any activity that involves a great amount of stress on the joints like, Tennis, Golf, Baseball, Basketball, Crossfit, Weightlifting / Powerlifting, Volleyball and more!</li>
<li>You’ll be able to enjoy exceptional elbow support while still maintaining your peak performance and a full range of arm motion.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Type: Adjustable Stabilising</li>
<li>Color: Available in different colors</li>
<li>Item Type: Body Shaper</li>
<li>Style: BodySuits</li>
<li>Material: Elastic</li>
<li>Size Type: Regular</li>
<li>Gender: Men/Women</li>
<li>Rise Type: High-Rise</li>
<li>Features: Slimming</li>
</ul>
<h3>Instructions</h3>
<ul>
<li>Wash in mild suds and rinse several times in clear water</li>
<li>Roll in towel to absorb moisture and dry flat</li>
<li>Do not iron</li>
<li>Do not use dryer</li>
<li>Latex-free</li>
</ul>
<h3>Size Available:</h3>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Elbow Size</th>
<th>Cap Size</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>7″ – 8″</td>
<td>Small</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>9″ – 10″</td>
<td>Medium</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>11″ – 12″</td>
<td>Large</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>13″ – 14″</td>
<td>Extra Large</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elbow-cap/">Elbow Cap, Healthgenie Compression Stabilizer, Adjustable And Pain Relief Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/elbow-cap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">971</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reusable Incontinence Underpads</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/reusable-incontinence-underpads/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/product/reusable-incontinence-underpads/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Save significantly on incontinence care costs. Our reusable underpads draw moisture away from the body and prevent skin irritation. For adults seeking solutions to frequent incontinence problems due to weak or overactive bladders, stop stressful sleepless nights fighting your overactive bladder urges. Sleep better knowing you won't have to get up several times through-out the night to change the sheets. Multiple layers prevent wetness from spreading to the bed - the soft, 3-ply, quilted fabric works much like an egg crate and add a soft layer to firm mattresses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/reusable-incontinence-underpads/">Reusable Incontinence Underpads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical&#8217;s enviornmentally friendly Reusable Underpad is made for durability with a special 3-ply fabric construction:</p>
<ul>
<li>The top outer layer is created with soft wick material for whisking away moisture and assures maximum comfort.</li>
<li>The 2nd layer is a heavy-duty soaker with the ability to double it&#8217;s weight in absorbency. It&#8217;s crafted from a heavy-duty felt material specifically designed for absorbing body fluids.</li>
<li>The bottom layer is made from a special Fablon barrier we call Unishield &#8211; it is 100% waterproof and will never crack even after 200 washings.</li>
</ul>
<p>Simply lay one of AT Surgical&#8217;s Reusable Underpad Waterproof Mattress Liners on top of the sheets and remove when necessary. It&#8217;s also a great alternative to frequent laundry loads and is less wasteful than disposable incontinence products. You can even layer up the Reusable Underpad for additional protection. No matter what stage of life you&#8217;re in, our Reusable Underpad mattress protector offers the relief and peace of mind you need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/reusable-incontinence-underpads/">Reusable Incontinence Underpads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">743</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adjustable Wrist Support Brace With Splints For Carpal Tunnel, Injuries, Wrist Pain, Sprain</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/product/naugahyde-adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace-w-contour-splint-right-or-left-side/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our high quality, sturdy, and durable brace is made with lightweight breathable neoprene. This means that it will be cool, comfortable and soft on your&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace/">Adjustable Wrist Support Brace With Splints For Carpal Tunnel, Injuries, Wrist Pain, Sprain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our high quality, sturdy, and durable brace is made with lightweight breathable neoprene. This means that it will be cool, comfortable and soft on your skin! Extra inner lining ensures no abrasions or marks on your hand. Removable metal splint keeps your hand in a neutral resting position that ensures wrist stability and promote healing. Made for people with carpal tunnel syndrome, wrist pain, numbness and tingling, arthritis, tendonitis etc. Now, let’s see how great it is. </p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<li>Elastic supports wrist joint</li>
<li>Durable Naugahyde® </li>
<li>Removable metal splint </li>
<li>Velcro® close, easy adjustment </li>
<li>Fully washable</li>
<li>Soft padded material for comfort</li>
<li>This product has Elastic supports that allow you to adjust the compression, and it also retains therapeutic heat.</li>
<h3>Product Specifications:</h3>
<li>Item Type: Wrist Support</li>
<li>Function: Protecting Muscle, Providing Support, Relieving Pain</li>
<li>Material: elastic tension fabric</li>
<li>Color: skin color</li>
<li>Washable: Fully washable</li>
<h3>Size: </h3>
<li>Size available </li>
<li>Free size</li>
<p><center></p>
<table style="undefined;table-layout: fixed; width: 410px">
<colgroup>
<col style="width: 195px">
<col style="width: 215px">
</colgroup>
<tr>
<th>Wrist Circumference</th>
<th>Brace Size</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>4.5&#8243; &#8211; 5.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Extra Small</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>5.5&#8243; &#8211; 6.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Small</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>6.5&#8243; &#8211; 7.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Medium</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>7.5&#8243; &#8211; 8.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Large</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>8.5&#8243; &#8211; 9.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Extra Large</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p></center></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace/">Adjustable Wrist Support Brace With Splints For Carpal Tunnel, Injuries, Wrist Pain, Sprain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/adjustable-velcro-wrist-brace/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">701</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arm Sling Shoulder Support With Strap, Elbow Brace, Lightweight &#038; Breathable</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/arm-sling/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/arm-sling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=258</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you still worried about the problems of hanging on the neck, the support area is not enough, the fixation is unstable, and the design&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/arm-sling/">Arm Sling Shoulder Support With Strap, Elbow Brace, Lightweight &#038; Breathable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you still worried about the problems of hanging on the neck, the support area is not enough, the fixation is unstable, and the design is too ugly? DON’T WORRY AT ALL, all the concerns are solved by our Arm Sling Support, that helps you comfortably wear it for a quick recovery. Now, let’s see how great it is.</p>
<h3>Main Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>The Arm Sling Support w/ Velcro Closure provides relief and protection while you’re recuperating and healing from an arm or hand fracture, sprain or surgery</li>
<li>Made with a 1″ wide adjustable strap and Velcro closures</li>
<li>The Arm Sling Support helps distribute weight to the shoulder and back</li>
<li>Reversible for the right or left arm</li>
<li>One size – adjustable</li>
<li>Made of premium fabric and ribbon material, great breath-ability.</li>
<li>Cross shoulder strap design, will not strangle the neck, comfortable to wear.</li>
<li>The shoulder strap can be adjusted easily to fit for different figures.</li>
<li>Stronger stability and flexibility.</li>
<li>Universal style design to fit for men and women.</li>
<li>Easy to wear or remove without tools required.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specifications:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Material: Velcro</li>
<li>Color: White/Blue</li>
<li>Shoulder Strap: Adjustable</li>
<li>Applications: This arm sling shoulder support is great for shoulder arm wrist cuff support, fracture and dislocation recovery etc.</li>
<li>Dimensions 4 x 1.25 x 8.5 in</li>
</ul>
<h3>Size:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Size available</li>
<li>Free size</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/arm-sling/">Arm Sling Shoulder Support With Strap, Elbow Brace, Lightweight &#038; Breathable</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/arm-sling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">258</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rib Injury Binder Belt Protector Wrap For Sore, Bruised Chest Support  With Abdominal Muscle Pain Treatment.</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/rib-belt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/product/mens-rib-belt-9-tall/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Specifically designed to provide stabilization and support to your sore rib cage to help treat injuries and pain caused by rib fractures, sprains, and more.&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/rib-belt/">Rib Injury Binder Belt Protector Wrap For Sore, Bruised Chest Support  With Abdominal Muscle Pain Treatment.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Specifically designed to provide stabilization and support to your sore rib cage to help treat injuries and pain caused by rib fractures, sprains, and more. Hold the rib cage in the proper position and ensures proper posture while reducing everyday pain caused by sudden movements. This Rib Belt is prescribed for patients with injured broken ribs, and broken sternum while offering middle and upper back supports. This belt ensures superior stabilization and sustaining rib and sternum injuries. Following surgery and surgical incisions, this belt can also provide supporting pressure for the patient. Made of high-quality materials for optimal comfort and breathability.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Breathable bandage repeats your anatomical shape</li>
<li>Fits around your ribs precisely according to your body form</li>
<li>Effectively reduce any kind of chest pain after the local surgery or any other possible rib and sternum traumas</li>
<li>Comfortable help you to heal faster</li>
<li>Used as prevention against muscle overload during exercises</li>
<li>Designed To Treat &amp; Protect:</li>
<li>Broken ribs</li>
<li>Sore or bruised rib cage</li>
<li>Cracked ribs</li>
<li>Intercostal muscle strain</li>
<li>Dislocated ribs</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Type: Belt</li>
<li>Color: White</li>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
<li>Body Part: Spinal Column</li>
<li>Structure: Flexible</li>
<li>Texture: Soft</li>
<li>Intended Use: Abdominal &amp; Rib Support</li>
<li>Package includes: 1pc X Relive Rib Belt</li>
</ul>
<h3>Size</h3>
<ul>
<li>Size Available</li>
<li>S 27 &#8211; 32”</li>
<li>M 33 &#8211; 38”</li>
<li>L 39 &#8211; 44”</li>
<li>XL 45 &#8211; 50”</li>
</ul>
<p>Directions: Simply wrap the rib binder around your chest directly below the breasts. Secure via Velcro closure to your desired compression level. Adjust as needed. For the women&#8217;s style, make sure the curved portion of the binder is centered underneath your breasts.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/rib-belt/">Rib Injury Binder Belt Protector Wrap For Sore, Bruised Chest Support  With Abdominal Muscle Pain Treatment.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">689</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pull On Wrist Support</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?post_type=product&#038;p=562</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This professionally designed hand and wrist support helps relieve pain, stiffness, swelling, irritation, cramping and hand fatigue.</p>
<p>Recommended in case of fractures, after removal of a cast or injures to ligament, muscles and tendons, our wrist support brace helps to return strength to your hand and wrist. All-day support with breathable, durable, soft and latex free materials.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/">Pull On Wrist Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-vertical a-spacing-none">
<li class="showHiddenFeatureBullets"><span class="a-list-item">Wrist support protects during exercise and healing</span></li>
<li class="showHiddenFeatureBullets"><span class="a-list-item">Pull over style allows you to wear and remove one-handed</span></li>
<li class="showHiddenFeatureBullets"><span class="a-list-item">Removable splint keeps the brace versatile</span></li>
</ul>
<p><center></p>
<table style="undefined;table-layout: fixed; width: 373px;">
<colgroup>
<col style="width: 178px;" />
<col style="width: 195px;" /> </colgroup>
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Palm Size</th>
<th>Brace Size</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2.5&#8243; &#8211; 3&#8243;</td>
<td>Small</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>3&#8243; &#8211; 3.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Medium</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>3.5&#8243; &#8211; 4&#8243;</td>
<td>Large</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>4&#8243; &#8211; 4.5&#8243;</td>
<td>Extra Large</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p></center></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/">Pull On Wrist Support</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/pull-on-wrist-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">562</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Hernia Truss Support Belt</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical's Hernia Trusses are made with a soft pad that applies gradual pressure and support to the weakened muscles of the groin with focused compression on the hernia. Designed to provide relief from an a reducible inguinal hernia in your groin - post or pre-surgery. The inguinal hernia truss will provide you with the support and comfort needed to maintain your active lifestyle.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/">AT Surgical Hernia Truss Support Belt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Inguinal Hernia Truss is designed to provide relief from a reducible inguinal hernia in your groin &#8211; post or pre-surgery</li>
<li>Provides constant, comfortable and adjustable pressure to the hernia</li>
<li>Over-the-brief style of hernia support, worn inconspicuously under clothing &#8211; may be used while bathing or swimming</li>
<li>Get some relief from a reducible inguinal hernia with the inguinal/groin hernia truss</li>
<li>Easy to slip on and off</li>
<li>Made in the USA</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Sizing</strong> (<em>Measure around hips</em>)</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>S</strong> <em>(26-30&#8243;)</em>, <strong>M</strong> <em>(32-36&#8243;)</em>, <strong>L</strong><em> (38-42&#8243;)</em> and <strong>XL</strong> <em>(44-48&#8243;)</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/category/hernias/">Learn more about hernias from our hernia section on our Articles page</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/">AT Surgical Hernia Truss Support Belt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/inguinal-groin-hernia-truss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">657</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 266/409 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-27 17:53:24 by W3 Total Cache
-->