<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product-category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 11:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Face Mask For Children&#8217;s</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/children-masks/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/children-masks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Lopez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 11:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7843</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Covered with soft cotton interior and exterior</li>
<li>Prevents irritation to sensitive skin</li>
<li>Durable, washable and reusable</li>
<li>Comfortable &#38; Secure</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/children-masks/">AT Surgical Face Mask For Children&#8217;s</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The AT Surgical Face masks are a comfortable and personal way to satisfy your safety needs. The seamless design makes for a sleek look while both maximizing comfort and allowing for your choice of our many stylish design options. Our range of designs is made to appeal to not only men and women but we also provide a stylish option for children. Designed for all-day or situational comfort and is 100% washable to maintain its reusability. Unlike disposable masks, our masks also have adjustable straps and construction that maintains high durability for any everyday situations. Our mask’s cotton interior provides a soft cushion for your face will minimizing any possible irritation that could occur when wearing a mask for a long period of time. The cotton exterior is also soft to the touch and the construction of the mask makes it foldable to provide easy storage when not in use</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/children-masks/">AT Surgical Face Mask For Children&#8217;s</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/children-masks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7843</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Mask For Adults</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/mask-prototype/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/mask-prototype/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Lopez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 11:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Covered with soft cotton interior and exterior</li>
<li>Prevents irritation to sensitive skin</li>
<li>Durable, washable and reusable</li>
<li>Comfortable &#38; Secure</li>
<li>Comes in many stylish options</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/mask-prototype/">AT Surgical Mask For Adults</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The AT Surgical Face masks are a comfortable and personal way to satisfy your safety needs. The seamless design makes for a sleek look while both maximizing comfort and allowing for your choice of our many stylish design options. Our range of designs is made to appeal to not only men and women but we also provide a stylish option for children. Designed for all-day or situational comfort and is 100% washable to maintain its reusability. Unlike disposable masks, our masks also have adjustable straps and construction that maintains high durability for any everyday situations. Our mask’s cotton interior provides a soft cushion for your face will minimizing any possible irritation that could occur when wearing a mask for a long period of time. The cotton exterior is also soft to the touch and the construction of the mask makes it foldable to provide easy storage when not in use. Easy to put on and remove freely and come in three sizes (Small, Medium, Large) to accommodate people of all sizes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/mask-prototype/">AT Surgical Mask For Adults</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/mask-prototype/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7837</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Regular Quilted Bottom Reusable / Washable Body Movers With 3 Handles 34&#8243; X 54”</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-regular-quilted-bottom-reusable-washable-body-movers-with-3-handles-34-x-54/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-regular-quilted-bottom-reusable-washable-body-movers-with-3-handles-34-x-54/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[William Lopez]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; AT Surgical underpads are washable and extremely comfortable for patients. The material on the top of the bed pad is a soft blend of&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-regular-quilted-bottom-reusable-washable-body-movers-with-3-handles-34-x-54/">AT Surgical Regular Quilted Bottom Reusable / Washable Body Movers With 3 Handles 34&#8243; X 54”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>AT Surgical underpads are washable and extremely comfortable for patients. The material on the top of the bed pad is a soft blend of natural and synthetic fibers. The cotton/polyester blend faces the patient. These underpads are completely leak-proof, making things quite convenient for the nurses and other medical care providers. They can be washed many times and due to being lightweight, they dry quickly. With the reusable underpads that Trifecta offers, it is far easier for a healthcare provider to make a quick change of the underpad rather than of the entire bottom sheet. Also, by using these underpads, the moisture will be absorbed by the pad itself. This keeps the patient dry and prevents the mattresses from being ruined.<br />
Cardinal Reusable quilted cotton-blend dry-touch top layer wicks moisture into the pad protecting the skin and maintaining skin wellness, a poly/rayon super absorbent layer absorbs and traps fluids, and a 100% waterproof vinyl backed polyester backing locks out moisture and staining. Bed Pads have added protection at the center where it is needed most. Machine washable and dry with bleach. Latex-free and lead-free. A non-slip bottom layer keeps the pad flat and in place.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Waterproof Barrier</li>
<li>Heavyweight Soaker</li>
<li>Multi-wash performance</li>
<li>Non-slip bottom layer keeps the pad in place</li>
<li>Added protection at the center where needed most</li>
<li>Machine wash and dry with bleach</li>
<li>Skin-friendly and heat-free soft fabric, Highly hygienic, breathable and durable</li>
<li>Reusable, economical and lightweight, Oeko-Tex quality standard</li>
<li>Can be sterilized up to 90 degree Celsius</li>
<li>Useful for babies and adults</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
<li>Washable: Yes</li>
<li>Texture: Semi-Soft</li>
<li>Material: Cotton/polyester</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes:</h3>
<ul>
<li>1 Size</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-regular-quilted-bottom-reusable-washable-body-movers-with-3-handles-34-x-54/">AT Surgical Regular Quilted Bottom Reusable / Washable Body Movers With 3 Handles 34&#8243; X 54”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-regular-quilted-bottom-reusable-washable-body-movers-with-3-handles-34-x-54/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7748</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women High Waist Body Shaper Tummy Slimming Control Waist Shapewear</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/women-high-waist-body-shaper-tummy-slimming-control-waist-shapewear/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/women-high-waist-body-shaper-tummy-slimming-control-waist-shapewear/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 06:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MATERIALS: 85% PA Nylon and 15% EA Elastane.SIZE &#38; COLOR: It comes with 5 sizes (S,M,L,XL,XXL) and 3 colors (Black, White and Nude).THONG STYLE SHAPEWEAR: Relief back pain, tummy control, lift your butt, provides back support.STRONG SHAPING EFFECT: The high compression product gives a strong shaping effect on your body and reduce the body size immediately once put on.COMFORTABLE: Soft microfiber is used which makes it comfortable to wear. It is a great item for day-long activities. This product is so thin that it is invisible under the clothes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/women-high-waist-body-shaper-tummy-slimming-control-waist-shapewear/">Women High Waist Body Shaper Tummy Slimming Control Waist Shapewear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the FarmaCell Basic compression and shaping products line, made by soft microfiber. All the products in the BODY SHAPER line make a high compression to the body with the result to have a STRONG SHAPING effect and reduce the body size immediately once put on.</p>
<p>The compression bandages incorporated in the products make also a modeling effect to make better body silhouette and in some products a great push-up effect.</p>
<p>Products are thin and invisible under the clothes. Products are made in 5 size and 3 colors, Black, White, and Nude.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Color: Black, White, Nude</li>
<li>100% New and high quality.</li>
<li>Materials: 85% PA Nylon and 15% EA Elastane, which is strong, elastic, stretchable and smooth.</li>
<li>Sweat-free comfort, antibacterial, moisture wicking. High quality fabric breathable and comfortable enough to be worn all day long. Hand-washing only.</li>
<li>These lightweight panties are easy care, washable and reusable. No one will ever know you have them on, but they will notice your sexy new curves.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/women-high-waist-body-shaper-tummy-slimming-control-waist-shapewear/">Women High Waist Body Shaper Tummy Slimming Control Waist Shapewear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/women-high-waist-body-shaper-tummy-slimming-control-waist-shapewear/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7568</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Ostomy Colostomy Pouch Bag Cover support. Belly bands</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-ostomy-colostomy-pouch-bag-cover-support-belly-bands/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-ostomy-colostomy-pouch-bag-cover-support-belly-bands/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7473</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical Anyone with an ostomy knows about skin irritation and discretion. This pouch cover solves both issues. By choosing a soft fabric in an&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-ostomy-colostomy-pouch-bag-cover-support-belly-bands/">AT Surgical Ostomy Colostomy Pouch Bag Cover support. Belly bands</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical Anyone with an ostomy knows about skin irritation and discretion. This pouch cover solves both issues. By choosing a soft fabric in an appealing print, skin issues and discretion are resolved. Since there are a huge variety of bags and pouches on the market, these instructions will guide you through making a custom pattern for any shape and size.<br />
Belly belt on a pregnant woman. Belly belts support the lower back and hips. Belly bands are flexible tube-like garments that women wear around the belly to extend the life of pre-pregnancy clothing by covering unbuttoned or unzipped pants. They also act as a layer to help cover areas of skin that become exposed as the belly expands. Some belly bands provide mild compression and may offer the hips and lower back an element of support. Belly bands remain popular among pregnant women and come in many different sizes, shapes, colors, and designs. They often have some elastic or a rubber trim to help prevent them from bunching up. Belly bands are sometimes called belly sleeves or maternity or pregnancy bands.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Stoma Cover made of Print Fabric</li>
<li>Colour: Blue</li>
<li>Material: 80% Polyester, 20% Cotton</li>
<li>I wear this covers with Coloplast SenSura Mio 1 Piece drainable and closed</li>
<li>.Function: One-piece system, with high-quality clamp</li>
<li>Active Carbon Filter: The active carbon filter has the odors removal function, to prevent embarrassing odors</li>
<li>Non-woven Fabric&#8212;Non-woven fabric for PE puncturing film liner, soft and comfortable</li>
<li>Skin Barrier：high quality hydrocolloid material with a non-woven edge to make the stickiness longer.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes:</h3>
<ul>
<li>1 SIZE F/A</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-ostomy-colostomy-pouch-bag-cover-support-belly-bands/">AT Surgical Ostomy Colostomy Pouch Bag Cover support. Belly bands</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-ostomy-colostomy-pouch-bag-cover-support-belly-bands/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7473</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Medical Elastic  Rib Belt natural One Size Fits For Men &#038; Women</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-medical-elastic-rib-belt-natural-one-size-fits-for-men-women-7/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-medical-elastic-rib-belt-natural-one-size-fits-for-men-women-7/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 10:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical Rib Belts For Men &#38; Women Rib Belts For Men &#38; Women helps stabilize rib and sternum fractures by limiting expansion through compression.&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-medical-elastic-rib-belt-natural-one-size-fits-for-men-women-7/">AT Surgical Medical Elastic  Rib Belt natural One Size Fits For Men &#038; Women</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical Rib Belts For Men &amp; Women Rib Belts For Men &amp; Women helps stabilize rib and sternum fractures by limiting expansion through compression. Rib Belts For Men &amp; Women provides comfort and encourages more controlled breathing to help reduce pain. Rib Belts also provide support and compression to the muscles and soft tissues of the rib cage weakened by strain, trauma, overuse, inactivity, or surgery. Paneled Hinged Stitch: This innovative design has a simulated hinged stitch that creates separate panels for a more conforming, tapered fit with flexibility. Old style panel abdominal binders were connected with an open, crochet-like stitch that easily pinched the skin and left an opening for a swelling pool. Unique hinged stitch eliminates these problems. Latex-Free and Plush Lining: Comfortable and non-irritating for patients and caregivers with latex rubber sensitivities. True Woven Elastic Woven, as opposed to knit elastic, is the premium construction inelastic materials. The woven elastic gives firm and consistent compression power and can be cut without unraveling to accommodate drainage tubes. Hook Compatible Exterior Allows for a wider range of adjustability and easy application. Indications Rib Belts For Men &amp; Women are indicated to support the rib cage and sternum by limiting expansion through compression. Goals Increase rib/sternum compression. Decrease anti-inflammatory medications. Decrease back pain symptoms. Low profile support. Breathable back support.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Paneled Hinged Stitch</li>
<li>Latex-Free and Plush Lining:</li>
<li>True Woven Elastic</li>
<li>The woven elastic gives firm and consistent compression power and can be cut without unraveling to accommodate drainage tubes</li>
<li>Hook Compatible Exterior</li>
<li>Provides even distribution of pressure</li>
<li>Velcro closure for easy application and removal</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Size: One Size Fits Most (Unisex)</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-medical-elastic-rib-belt-natural-one-size-fits-for-men-women-7/">AT Surgical Medical Elastic  Rib Belt natural One Size Fits For Men &#038; Women</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-medical-elastic-rib-belt-natural-one-size-fits-for-men-women-7/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7471</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support CRADLE SLING WHITE/BLUE for fracture, sprain or surgery</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-cradle-sling-white-blue-for-fracture-sprain-or-surgery/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-cradle-sling-white-blue-for-fracture-sprain-or-surgery/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 12:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical the Universal Cradle Arm Sling provides well-balanced support to the arm or hand during recuperation from fracture, sprain or surgery. Recuperate in comfort.&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-cradle-sling-white-blue-for-fracture-sprain-or-surgery/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support CRADLE SLING WHITE/BLUE for fracture, sprain or surgery</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical the Universal Cradle Arm Sling provides well-balanced support to the arm or hand during recuperation from fracture, sprain or surgery. Recuperate in comfort. Simply strap on the Universal Cradle Sling, and get on with your day. The cradle sling helps provide comfortable relief and protection while you&#8217;re recuperating and healing. Constructed with a 1&#8243; wide adjustable strap and Velcro closure. The Universal Cradle Arm Sling helps distribute weight to the shoulder and back. The pouch is made of lightweight, washable-poly/cotton wrinkle-resistant fabric. Our cradle sling is a cost-effective option for all term arm support following an arm injury where you need to support the arm in a fixed position during recovery. This cradle sling is comfortable to wear and effective. These cradle slings are one of the best for quality and price.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Comfortable and easy to wash.</li>
<li>More durable and lasts longer.</li>
<li>For patients that will be wearing a sling for a long time</li>
<li>Reversible for the right or left arm</li>
<li>Long-life durability through many normal wash cycles.</li>
<li>Adjustable strap for customizable compression</li>
<li>Ideal for fracture, sprain or surgery</li>
<li>Faster Recovery</li>
<li>Tested and crafted to perfection</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Condition: A brand-new, unused, unopened, undamaged item</li>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
<li>Texture: Semi-soft</li>
<li>Use: Arms</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Sizes Available</li>
<li>1 SIZE F/A</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-cradle-sling-white-blue-for-fracture-sprain-or-surgery/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support CRADLE SLING WHITE/BLUE for fracture, sprain or surgery</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-cradle-sling-white-blue-for-fracture-sprain-or-surgery/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7462</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling W/SWATHE White / Blue for Injured</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-w-swathe-white-blue-for-injured/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-w-swathe-white-blue-for-injured/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 12:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical provides comfortable arm support and helps to fix the arm in a desired resting position following an arm injury. Adjustable height strap to&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-w-swathe-white-blue-for-injured/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling W/SWATHE White / Blue for Injured</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical provides comfortable arm support and helps to fix the arm in a desired resting position following an arm injury. Adjustable height strap to immobilize and support the arm in the most comfortable position quickly and easily. Helps stabilize arm to relieve pain and prevent re-injury and remove pressure points. Whether recuperating from an injury, recovering from surgery, or seeking to alleviate shoulder, arm or wrist pain. This reversible design also allows for strap adjustments to be made while wearing the sling. Lightweight and breathable materials for comfortable all-day wear. Neoprene Free, Made from Latex-Free Materials, Includes Shoulder Pad for Comfort. Our arm sling is a cost-effective option for all term arm support following an arm injury where you need to support the arm in a fixed position during recovery. This arm sling is comfortable to wear and effective. These arm slings are one of the best for the quality and price.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Comfortable and easy to wash.</li>
<li>More durable and lasts longer.</li>
<li>For patients that will be wearing a sling for a long time</li>
<li>Long life durability through many normal wash cycles.</li>
<li>Adjustable strap for customizable compression</li>
<li>Ideal for injured arms</li>
<li>Faster Recovery</li>
<li>Tested and crafted to perfection</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Condition: A brand-new, unused, unopened, undamaged item</li>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
<li>Texture: Semi-soft</li>
<li>Use: Arms</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Sizes Available</li>
<li>1 SIZE F/A</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-w-swathe-white-blue-for-injured/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling W/SWATHE White / Blue for Injured</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-w-swathe-white-blue-for-injured/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7461</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling IMM. White/Blue for Injured</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-imm-white-blue-for-injured/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-imm-white-blue-for-injured/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[EcomClips]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 12:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/?post_type=product#038;p=7460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical provides comfortable arm support and helps to fix the arm in a desired resting position following an arm injury. Adjustable height strap to&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-imm-white-blue-for-injured/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling IMM. White/Blue for Injured</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AT Surgical provides comfortable arm support and helps to fix the arm in a desired resting position following an arm injury. Adjustable height strap to immobilize and support the arm in the most comfortable position quickly and easily. Helps stabilize arm to relieve pain and prevent re-injury and remove pressure points. Whether recuperating from an injury, recovering from surgery, or seeking to alleviate shoulder, arm or wrist pain. This reversible design also allows for strap adjustments to be made while wearing the sling. Lightweight and breathable materials for comfortable all-day wear. Neoprene Free, Made from Latex-Free Materials, Includes Shoulder Pad for Comfort. Our arm sling is a cost-effective option for all term arm support following an arm injury where you need to support the arm in a fixed position during recovery. This arm sling is comfortable to wear and effective. These arm slings are one of the best for the quality and price.</p>
<h3>Features:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Comfortable and easy to wash.</li>
<li>More durable and lasts longer.</li>
<li>For patients that will be wearing a sling for a long time</li>
<li>Long life durability through many normal wash cycles.</li>
<li>Adjustable strap for customizable compression</li>
<li>Ideal for injured arms</li>
<li>Faster Recovery</li>
<li>Tested and crafted to perfection</li>
</ul>
<h3>Specification:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Condition: A brand-new, unused, unopened, undamaged item</li>
<li>Gender: Unisex</li>
<li>Texture: Semi-soft</li>
<li>Use: Arms</li>
</ul>
<h3>Sizes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Sizes Available</li>
<li>1 SIZE F/A</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-imm-white-blue-for-injured/">AT Surgical Comfort Arm Support Sling IMM. White/Blue for Injured</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/at-surgical-comfort-arm-support-sling-imm-white-blue-for-injured/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">7460</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 157/679 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-27 17:56:25 by W3 Total Cache
-->