<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Disease &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<atom:link href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/category/disease/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<description>Manufacturers of Orthopedic Braces and Supports since 1975</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 18:50:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/cropped-tiny-doc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Disease &#8211; AT Surgical</title>
	<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">140757076</site>	<item>
		<title>Zika Virus FAQ: Symptoms &#038; More</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/zika-map-virus-and-symptoms/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/zika-map-virus-and-symptoms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[delta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 16:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Disease]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides & Primers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Fitness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Curious about the latest epidemic to grace our planet? Read more to learn more! Q: Where did it come from? A: Zika Forest In 1947 in&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/zika-map-virus-and-symptoms/">Zika Virus FAQ: Symptoms &#038; More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Curious about the latest epidemic to grace our planet? Read more to learn more!</h4>
<p><span id="more-3180"></span></p>
<h3>Q: Where did it come from?<br />
A: Zika Forest</h3>
<p>In 1947 in Uganda, a virus spread by day active mosquitos was first isolated in the Zika Forest of Uganda. Named the Zika Virus, this relative to dengue, yellow fever, and West Nile was limited to a narrow band of land on the equator until 2007, when it crossed the Pacific Ocean and created an epidemic in 2015-2016.</p>
<h3>Q: What are the symptoms of the Zika virus?<br />
A: Symptoms may include fever, pain, fatigue, &amp; chills</h3>
<p>The illness caused by the Zika virus is called Zika fever. As is often the case, symptoms are mild to non-existent. Symptoms last for about a week and include fever, red eyes, joint pain, headache, and rash, and as of this writing there are no deaths caused by the virus. <em>However</em>, infection during pregnancy can cause microcephaly and other brain malformations during the development of the fetus that have lifelong consequences for the baby.</p>
<h3>Q: What is a Zika baby?<br />
A: A child who suffers from Congenital Zika Syndrome</h3>
<p>This throwaway term refers to the birth defects caused by Zika fever during pregnancy. <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/zika/healtheffects/birth_defects.html">Learn more about Congenital Zika syndrome here</a>.</p>
<h3>Q: What are the treatment options for Zika virus?<br />
A: Rest &amp; Fluids</h3>
<p>There are no vaccines or cures for Zika fever. Recovery is a matter of getting plenty of rest, pushing fluids, and treating the symptoms. Do not treat with medication before talking to your doctor. Reduce fever and pain with acetaminophen, do not take aspirin or other non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs until Dengue is ruled out.</p>
<h3>Q: What areas are affected by the Zika virus?<br />
A: Any area with day-active mosquitos on or near the equator, for now</h3>
<p>This is the current distribution:</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3182 aligncenter" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/elife-zika-map_custom-7e7b44ae3fd3215c8d7d89d5ddb6312bddee903f-s900-c85.jpg" /></p>
<p>However, thanks to the effects of global warming, any area on the map below could become effected with the rise of a few degrees in temperature:</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3210 aligncenter" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Zika-Dengue-Chikungunya-albopictus-mosquito-distribution.jpg" /></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/zika-map-virus-and-symptoms/">Zika Virus FAQ: Symptoms &#038; More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/zika-map-virus-and-symptoms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3180</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Steps for Great Diabetes Foot Care</title>
		<link>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/5-steps-diabetes-foot-care/</link>
					<comments>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/5-steps-diabetes-foot-care/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[May]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Diabetes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disease]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3f4.98b.myftpupload.com/?p=3041</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Diabetes foot care is not usually a big concern with people, the main concern for those with diabetes is regulating blood sugar. However, to many&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/5-steps-diabetes-foot-care/">Top 5 Steps for Great Diabetes Foot Care</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Diabetes foot care is not usually a big concern with people, the main concern for those with diabetes is regulating blood sugar. However, to many patients&#8217; surprise &#8211; the symptoms do not stop there. Nearly 70 percent of people with diabetes, have some form of neuropathy. This is damage of the nerves in the hands or feet from poor or low circulation. Symptoms include lose of feeling in the hands and feet, or higher risk of infection. Here are 5 steps for taking care of your feet with diabetes.</p>
<p><span id="more-3041"></span></p>
<h2>Diabetes Foot Care</h2>
<h2><em>Step 1:<br />
</em>Inspect your feet daily</h2>
<p>Patients should check their feet daily, to make sure no new discolorations, sores, or cracked/dry skin occur. Using a mirror for the under side of your feet, make sure you check the entire foot. Have someone help you if you cannot manage.</p>
<h2><em>Step 2:</em><br />
Check water temperature accurately</h2>
<p>With intensive damage to the nerves of your feet and hands, you might find it harder to know when water is too hot. Hot tubs, baths/showers, and doing dishes can become a huge problem if the water is too hot and you cannot feel it. This can lead to scalding burns and blisters &#8211; which invite infection. Using your elbow will help you keep accurate readings of water temps.</p>
<h2><em>Step 3:</em><br />
Invest in good footwear and socks</h2>
<p>Shoe shopping with a diabetes sufferer can become a real task. Making sure you have the right footwear and accessories is very important. Some tips include: looking for deeper toe boxes, and optimal coverage on the top and bottom of the foot. Also shying away from shoes and socks with seams inside that can rub against your feet. Socks should have padding and be really good at wicking away moisture. Check out our great <a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/product/knee-high-compression-support-stockings-with-closed-toe/">compression socks</a>!</p>
<h2><em>Step 4: </em><br />
Don&#8217;t go barefoot!</h2>
<p>Along with checking water temperatures, you should never go barefoot in your own home. Nerve damage significantly decreases the foot&#8217;s ability to feel for any objects. Stepping on a lego isn&#8217;t a concern, but a thumbtack or getting a splinter becomes deadly. You may not feel the object cut or scrape your foot &#8211; allowing infection to grow and spread.</p>
<h2><em>Step 5: </em><br />
Orthotics are your friend</h2>
<p>Keeping comfort in mind, getting a good pair of inserts can get be helpful. You can find great gel inserts for much less than a new pair of shoes, and for a whole lot more impact. We sell great inserts, like <a href="https://atsurgical.myftpupload.com/product/dual-durometer-silicone-heel-cups/">these</a> or <a href="https://atsurgical.myftpupload.com/product/slim-silicone-insoles-34-thick-metatarsal-pad/">these</a>.</p>
<p>Taking your diabetes care one step at a time is important and helps make it more manageable. Always talk to your doctor for recommendations on new products and treatments that help you overcome the troubles that diabetes brings to your life.</p>
<p><a href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/diabetes-care.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-5608" src="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/diabetes-care.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="292" srcset="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/diabetes-care.jpg 600w, https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/diabetes-care-300x146.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Want more articles like this? Leave a rating:</h3>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/5-steps-diabetes-foot-care/">Top 5 Steps for Great Diabetes Foot Care</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/">AT Surgical</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://atsmanufacturing.github.io/oldat/5-steps-diabetes-foot-care/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">3041</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 131/170 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced (Requested URI contains query) 
Minified using disk

Served from: atsurgical.com @ 2023-04-27 17:40:48 by W3 Total Cache
-->